Krish NAik: Yeah, hello everyone, am I audible or not? Please let me know in the chats.
Krish NAik: All right.
Krish NAik: All right, guys, so, like, today we'll be talking about the same project, the continual discussion
Krish NAik: But today, a little bit task that I'll be doing, and you will be doing it in the live class.
Krish NAik: Okay, now, so let's talk about today's agenda. Okay, so let me start sharing my screen.
Krish NAik: I think, Zed, I think this is my set.
Krish NAik: Alright, which is my desktop, too.
Krish NAik: Alright, I think everybody can see my screen, please let me know.
Krish NAik: Because my settings are a bit different, so it's for a final change.
Krish NAik: Thank you.
Krish NAik: So, in the last class, everybody has done and tested the app. Please let me know, I think you've got enough time, 5 digs, to do the entire testing of the app. In last class, I think most of you have already done the testing, but please provide a confirmation, because the next step, always.
Krish NAik: like, Dockerization, once we have done the Docker step, then the next step is AWSDeployment.wilcom.
Krish NAik: Okay, so, like, common standards still now. So, like, in this particular deployment, so what are the things that we have already done? If you remember, I will just list down the main services through which we have done the deployment, and in future, what we'll be doing. So, if you remember, in Project 1, what was the actual service? Anybody remember?
Krish NAik: on which we have done the deployment, what was the actual name of the AWS service?
Krish NAik: Quickly tell me.
Krish NAik: Project 1, I think at least few people have attended Project 1, everybody. It was aptron, correct?
Krish NAik: If?
Krish NAik: Then, in the next project, What was the service? Quickly let me know, I'll just copypel that stuff?
Krish NAik: In that way.
Krish NAik: Things will be much more clear.
Krish NAik: Project 2 was about Lambda, correct?
Krish NAik: John?
Krish NAik: So, serverless Lambda.
Krish NAik: Meeting,
Krish NAik: Okay.
Krish NAik: Now, ugh.
Krish NAik: This time, I'll be picking up an easy service, okay, refer to as beanstalk.
Krish NAik: How many of you have worked with Beanstalk?
Krish NAik: Anybody previously, it's very, very easy, like.
Krish NAik: as compared to others. Then I think, ECS plus Farget, which we'll be doing with respect to the next one.
Krish NAik: And finally, our Kubernetes… this is actually… it will be an overkill, not required, but again, for the purpose of our main discussion, we'll be using EKS, so this is…
Krish NAik: COVID-19.
Krish NAik: Okay.
Krish NAik: So in this way, like, immediately these 5 services, any other services that you guys know, you can let me know in the chat.
Krish NAik: Because I think at least these are the 5 major AWS services. If I say which one is the easiest one, like AppRunner easy, Beanstalk easy, then Lambda, little bit complex, just because you need to handle the specific Lambda environment whenever you are working with container-based images, like last time we have done.
Krish NAik: Okay, a specific docker.lambda file with a mango adapter, which is required. Then, I think, Beanstalk, anybody else works with Beanstalk, please let me know in the chat.
Krish NAik: Yes or no?
Krish NAik: Yes or no, because, like, Beanstalk, actually takes… launches its own cloud formation, and there it will be launching the EC2 instance, everything automatically, you just need to just pass the command.
Krish NAik: Alright, you guys have not worked, okay? Then, alright, like, this is project 3, project 4, any other services out of this 5 that you guys know about? That's why I'm asking.
Krish NAik: Anybody else?
Krish NAik: people with AWS experience, anything.
Krish NAik: I think majorly fiber there, no. Other than that, anything else that you guys can think about?
Krish NAik: That's what I was thinking, because 5 projects, 5 different types, at least you guys should be familiar with the media services.
Krish NAik: Okay, no other services coming in mind. Alright, guys, fine, then leave it. Okay, because in this entire course, then, five things, and always remember that if you want to start from an MVP, from an MVP, and the next step, from where? Because these two are the main advanced ones that are actually used in production.
Krish NAik: These three?
Krish NAik: I can say, whenever you are working in an MBP, okay, or a POC, then these three are good.
Krish NAik: SageMaker deployment, what happens? SageMaker actually launches multiple services behind the scenes, Anish.
Krish NAik: core service I'm talking about.
Krish NAik: For example, if I say Beanstalk, I know that it will actually launch an EC2. Inside that EC2, your application will be running. So, the core service.
Krish NAik: Okay, I'm talking about core service.
Krish NAik: That's fine.
Krish NAik: Alright, fine. So, let's proceed ahead. So, I think today we'll be exploring this a little bit. Even I've not done the testing, but let's do it on the run.
Krish NAik: I was working in a work tree, so we will proceed ahead.
Krish NAik: I think, where is my text editor? Just wait, let me just open my text editor…
Krish NAik: Now I have a lot of other things open, just…
Krish NAik: Let's see, today we can complete it or not, otherwise… because the next agenda after this project, I think everybody remembers what we'll be discussing.
Krish NAik: Please let me know.
Krish NAik: GraphRag.
Krish NAik: Okay, after GraphRag, multimodal rag, and then it will be Project 4, and then, like, Haystack, I'll be taking that, and then Langraph will start. So, just keep it in your mind. GraphRag, multimodal rack, before that one haystack session that I can plan.
Krish NAik: Alright, so in our core application, if you remember, in the last class.
Krish NAik: What are the services that we have already discussed?
Krish NAik: Okay, because I think, ID part already I have discussed, because this is one of the first services.
Krish NAik: Then, re-ranking, I think re-ranking, I have not discussed, because in re-ranking, there are two types of re-ranker, the local one, and I hope everybody has tested the local as well as the watch.
Krish NAik: In the last class, people have done the testing, I know, but others told that they will be doing so. By this time, I hope that.
Krish NAik: Let's see, with respect to deployment, I cannot say that within one hour, a single script works, okay? Because I don't know, like, how many few people might
Krish NAik: do it from your end, and few people might get stuck. So, really, in… they cannot commit, tomorrow I can start crafting. Okay?
Krish NAik: Alright.
Krish NAik: So let's quickly talk about the remaining services. One is re-ranking. Okay, then, web search, I think this web service is pretty much self-explanatory.
Krish NAik: Please let me know.
Krish NAik: Because this is a direct, simple, tabuli call.
Krish NAik: to the Tavilion API.
Krish NAik: Because this is one of the easiest, services. Other than that, I don't think any other services are there which are done under 30 lines of code.
Krish NAik: Yes?
Krish NAik: Because the actual, this is the simple where I'm initializing the client, and from get settings, I'm getting the API key information, and I'm just making the call.
Krish NAik: So this is where I'm making the call to the API. Once I make the call, I'm capturing all those results through the response variable, and then I'm accessing it one by one.
Krish NAik: Okay? In those results, you'll be getting title, URL, content, and score.
Krish NAik: Now, this is the return type of the Tavili API. Okay, so pretty much self-explanatory stuff. The same thing if you want to do it with respect to XR, or DuckDuckGo, Brave, anywhere, the same thing happens.
Krish NAik: Now, in some APIs, you get, two-step, things. Like, first, it will ask you to do a scraping, like, first, it will do a fetch operation. Fetch means just it will hit the URL and it will just gather all the URLs. Once it has here…
Krish NAik: Once you will have all the URLs, then it will perform a scraping operation.
Krish NAik: Okay, so Firecrawl is another service which is widely used in production. So, three main services I have seen people are adopting. One is Fire Crawl, one is Tabuli, one is EXA, so anyone can be used in production.
Krish NAik: Alright, then comes, sparse vector service. In last class, already I have gone through the sparse vector service.
Krish NAik: 10, I think? Alright, self-reflective. Now, these implementations… how many of you have gone through this particular implementation of CRAG and self-reflective RAG? Because this is exactly the same thing, I've copy-pasted it from the notebook, but I'm much…
Krish NAik: I made the module a bit with respect to classes and much more functions, so that it becomes easier to debug.
Krish NAik: Yes?
Krish NAik: let me know, like, how many of you remember the CRAG and the self-rag component?
Krish NAik: Because in the last class, I have already discussed these things, guys. If you don't remember quickly, you can open your workflow folder, I think. Okay, and then you can actually look into this both mode. Okay, if you don't remember, for your quick reference, please go through this. That's why I've shared this.
Krish NAik: Okay, now this is the booth mode, a single mode check if you want to do, then you can actually check only the CRAC file, as well, because in the last class, I've already discussed all these things. There is nothing left.
Krish NAik: Alright, fine. So, the first step, if you guys remember, please let me know, can we start ahead with the next step, like, working with the deployment and other things?
Krish NAik: Yes.
Krish NAik: produce here, Mantaj. Alright, Mantach, that part I can do later on, okay? But right now, let's focus on the first part.
Krish NAik: Alright, then I think the first step, according to the notes, so let's start with the Docker one.
Krish NAik: Okay, now, whenever you are working with Docker, okay, so right now, in your Docker, if you remember in this project, you don't have a… what I can say.
Krish NAik: requirement.th. Okay, so first of all, let's get my main, like, the Docker script, okay? And then we will, check locally that everything is working fine or not.
Krish NAik: Okay, before that, one important thing, yes. Okay, so if you remember, I was using a local instance of Quadrant.
Krish NAik: In the last class, people were using the cloud instance, but right now, as I'll be deploying, I'll be switching it from local
Krish NAik: to cloud.
Krish NAik: Okay, so this particular switch, with respect to quadrant everybody, please make it.
Krish NAik: Because I know in last class, already it was shown you need the URL, quadrant URL, and you need the API key.
Krish NAik: Yes?
Krish NAik: Please let me know. I think everybody knows this, I don't need to show you this part.
Krish NAik: Few people might not have switched, but as we are right now deploying, there won't be anything local, so everything will be based on cloud. So please, be sure you have these environment variables. And to do a sign-up, I think everybody is comfortable. If somebody's not comfortable, please let me know in the chat.
Krish NAik: That I don't know about Quadrant.
Krish NAik: Let me know, let me know in the chat, guys, quickly.
Krish NAik: Because right now, as I'll be deploying, okay, so you just need to keep it in your .env, that's the only stuff.
Krish NAik: Let me know, yes, we have the credential, something like that, please let me know in the chat.
Krish NAik: Cloud Quadrant, yes, it's Qt Rand. Okay, but yes, you need the cloud credentials, because locally, as we were working with a Docker instance, as I'll be doing the deployment, so I'll be moving on to the cloud-based.
Krish NAik: For cloud-based, you need two things. The quadrant URL, the endpoint, and with that, the API key access.
Krish NAik: Only these two things. The rest automatically, like your creation of the collection and other things that will be taken care of. Okay, if you don't have, please take two minutes. I don't think you just need to do a, quadrant.tech, that is the website.
Krish NAik: Where is the website? Just wait?
Krish NAik: I think somewhere around.
Krish NAik: You'll try and talk back.
Krish NAik: Okay, just do a Google, sign-in here.
Krish NAik: I think in last class, most of you have done it, but if you have not done, just create a cluster. That's the bare minimum. Like, you can go to the… get set one, so for example…
Krish NAik: Okay.
Krish NAik: One is this one?
Krish NAik: Let me use the BS account only for now.
Krish NAik: Okay, like, you will be getting, so whenever you create your own account, you will be getting this create option, and under this create option, you can select, like, whatever the name of the cluster that you want to give, because this is a dedicated cluster.
Krish NAik: Okay, so that's why. Just pass the name. Keep the cluster version as the default one, select AWS. I was working with anything close to India that you can pick up, like Asia, Pacific, Mumbai works.
Krish NAik: Okay.
Krish NAik: So, I don't think any other things, by default, whatever the free settings that are coming, please do use that. Okay, so please create a free cluster. You don't have to pay anything for this.
Krish NAik: Once this part is done, then comes the next thing, which is with respect to your Dockerfile. So just wait, I think I need to get the Dockerfile contents. In the meantime, please be sure you have the Quadrant API key, and the…
Krish NAik: Endpoint with you guys.
Krish NAik: Let me just open.
Krish NAik: Please, let me know, then I will start with the…
Krish NAik: Docker file part. So, one by one, I'll be doing the push. It's not like, in one shot, I won't be doing everything.
Krish NAik: Please delete your… if… see, people won't be getting the option of a free cluster if you already have a cluster, that's why.
Krish NAik: Okay, so you have to understand that.
Krish NAik: Okay, MS, whoever is asking, like Rajat, people, I think if you already have a cluster, you won't be getting the option of a free cluster, okay? So please create or delete the old one.
Krish NAik: Okay, and then recreate or use the old one, whichever.
Krish NAik: I have no issues with that.
Krish NAik: If you have an existing collection in that cluster, automatically, in our case, a new collection will be created.
Krish NAik: Did we start with the quarter? No. As we are starting with the deployment part. So, from local, we are moving towards that cloud part. Rest, everything will be fine.
Krish NAik: Alright, so I think I can create a, UV log, alright.
Krish NAik: Please let me know once you guys have, done it.
Krish NAik: Because I need to push a few files, so that's what I'll be looking into.
Krish NAik: So, I think it would be better if I share my entire work tree folder only with you guys. Then you guys can directly copy-paste the same thing.
Krish NAik: Okay, so right now, this is two-step, if you remember in the last project also, as we are working with UV, because at least the speeds of UV are much better as compared. And the other thing you need to handle is…
Krish NAik: you're a dockling. If you remember in the last project, we have done the…
Krish NAik: that change of the default docklink, which uses GPU you need to switch back to.
Krish NAik: The CPU version. I think everyone remembers for that, we added one tag.
Krish NAik: Yes, and Project 2, the same thing that needs to be taken, care here also.
Krish NAik: Okay.
Krish NAik: So, let me, first of all, just wait. I think it's better,
Krish NAik: To delete this stuff once.
Krish NAik: controls. So, I'll be sharing, one new folder, just wait.
Krish NAik: Let me just delete this one now.
Krish NAik: Alright.
Krish NAik: So I'll be pushing a few files, I think.
Krish NAik: Okay, so…
Krish NAik: Mmm.
Krish NAik: Just wait, let me see what are the files that I have.
Krish NAik: Work trees, work trees, work trees, so majorly, I think, with respect to, alright, the entire folder I'm pushing to you.
Krish NAik: Now, this is a work tree. How many of you know about work trees in Git?
Krish NAik: Okay, so it's a specific workday folder that I am sharing, as I was only working with a single feature.
Krish NAik: Okay, so later on, you can actually test this out, and then you can actually proceed ahead with the next step. So, deployment files AWS.
Krish NAik: Okay, so I'll just complete.
Krish NAik: So I've shared, all the files with you, please do have a check, and you can do a git pull.
Krish NAik: So, automatically, this work series folder will be coming to you.
Krish NAik: Now, Mitesh is telling, I'm getting this quadrant client exception, response handling, no connection could be based because the target machine actively reduced. Mitesh, please do have a check, because in the last class, everybody has done that check, and they…
Krish NAik: Actually… Confirm that, please, that's working. The GitHub link is the same link, Santish Tiwari.
Krish NAik: It has not changed.
Krish NAik: If we want again, okay.
Krish NAik: This is the same one.
Krish NAik: You can… everybody can do a git pull, the only thing that,
Krish NAik: I think I have added in this… Alright.
Krish NAik: Hmm…
Krish NAik: I think this is the one, one minute ago.
Krish NAik: Alright, I think.
Krish NAik: Okay, because of this work trees and other things that's coming under it get ignored. Let me just remove those things.
Krish NAik: I thought it got pushed.
Krish NAik: Just retail.
Krish NAik: No, no, no, we haven't done nothing, so just…
Krish NAik: So I think, let me just go back to my project directory, I think.feiting, or…
Krish NAik: Yep, so now I think… Can't pass the entire thing.
Krish NAik: Please do have a check. I think, majorly I have added all the fixes.
Krish NAik: Let me see, because, specifically, I'm pushing on the specific tree, that's why I feel.
Krish NAik: Right now, I've removed, I think,
Krish NAik: Received, deploy, directory, because that's a dot one, okay? So, hidden one, but I have actually added it, so I think it should be pushed. Otherwise, manually, again, if I try to do it, dot dot dot, looks like…
Krish NAik: Okay.
Krish NAik: Can't see the folder. Okay, fine. Leave it. Manually, I'll be sharing it. Leave it, leave it. Yeah, okay, it is in the other branch? Yes, yes, yes, yes, that's why. Because I was, actually created a tree, that's why from here you will be getting all those files.
Krish NAik: Alright, guys. Now, see, what are the files that I have in this branch, and now I'll be doing the initial testing, so you guys can actually take a clone of this one, or you guys can write simply, like, git switch, and the name of this branch, which is deploy slash AWS hyphen b. Now, in this particular branch, what I have done?
Krish NAik: So, let's talk about the important files. One is the Docker file, which you can run, actually, from your own one. Okay, so now this file, what it does, so first of all, it will be taking the dependencies of all your UV. Okay, so for your UV, they have a separate, if you remember, a base image.
Krish NAik: Now, this is the base image for your UV, okay, and a few environment variables that we have kept for UV only. Like, UV will be using the torch backend as CPU and not as the GP one. Then, link mode, compile bytecode. Now, these are the default
Krish NAik: UV Docker Hub settings from the default image that I have picked up.
Krish NAik: Then comes your, work directory slash app.
Krish NAik: Okay, so that's why I feel that, this is fine. No, so on. Now, this is a different tree, actually. That's why that, new branch that was created.
Krish NAik: When you work with different trees, it is pretty much similar, just like. If you have worked with Git trees.
Krish NAik: Yep.
Krish NAik: Because whenever I do a testing, I don't do any testing directly on the main branch. It's better. One option, you create a separate branch, or you separate… create a separate work.
Krish NAik: Next slide.
Krish NAik: Now, the next thing, once I have, selected my work directory app from here, okay, then comes, these are a few of the installations. How many of you remember these are all installations?
Krish NAik: Now, these are docklink files and sentence performance requirements requirement.
Krish NAik: Okay? I've kept it bare minimum. If you remember, in the last project, we have added more APD gate.
Krish NAik: Installations.
Krish NAik: Okay, so, like, we will be doing a check, but for now, let's keep these things only.
Krish NAik: Then, your pyproject.tuml, this file already I have shared, the main requirements, alternate of requirement.txt. Then, in your system, whenever you have done an UV sync, automatically this UV log file will be generated in your case.
Krish NAik: Okay, and then you will sync, no dev, no installed project. Now, through this, you will be doing the installation of the packages.
Krish NAik: Whenever you are performing, you need the README file, because, when you do an UV sync from your PyProject.2ml, it will actually look for the README file is available or not.
Krish NAik: Okay, so that's why that, requirement of README file that I have. Then our entire app folder for my, source to destination that I'll be copying.
Krish NAik: Okay?
Krish NAik: Then comes, UV Sync, through which, again, my main installation of the packages will start. Now, this I've kept as a step to do the verification, that my sentence transformers is working. It means that there are certain dependencies if they are actually missing. This part won't work, guys.
Krish NAik: Okay, now really, like, this part, you have to do the debug. I've given you the high-level script for now, the same thing that I'll be doing the execution. Now, once your first part of UV is done, what is the next thing? To work, with your application-level stuff?
Krish NAik: Okay, now, for your application-level stuff, because these are all majorly OS-level dependencies, once your OS-level dependencies are sort, then you will come to application-level dependencies.
Krish NAik: Now, for your application-level dependencies, directly, I need a Python runtime. Once I have that, then, again, back to my code. So that's why, like, if you remember in Project 2, we have taken that approach of building the base image. So whenever you are working, that particular approach is better. Because this time, again, I'm not building the base image.
Krish NAik: But you should actually do that, because this will take more time.
Krish NAik: But, if you are working with the Dockling CPU, the time won't be very, very high, okay? So again, I am repeating that. Please use the Docklink
Krish NAik: CPU, don't use the GPU version.
Krish NAik: Alright, then these are a few security steps as per building a Docker image. It's a bad practice to execute anything from the root user, so it's a better practice to create a non-root user for security. Okay, and through that, you will be doing every execution within that Docker container.
Krish NAik: Okay, so that's by creating some necessary folders where my PDF files and other things that will be getting uploaded. Passing the ownership to that particular folder for the particular user that I am creating, which is the app user right now. So, to this particular user, here, as you can see, all the permissions.
Krish NAik: that I am providing.
Krish NAik: Okay, so user exposed 8000, because this is our main Fast API application. Okay, and finally, this is the main one through which… this is the entry point of our application, using the UVicon, one that we'll be doing.
Krish NAik: Okay, so right now, by default, keep the workers one, because in Beanstalk, you'll be having the option to do everything, like auto-scale and other stuff that can easily be done.
Krish NAik: Alright, now this is the first step. Once you have the Docker file.
Krish NAik: So, quickly tell me what you will do. I hope everybody remembers you will be doing a Docker build.
Krish NAik: Yes or no?
Krish NAik: Guys, please let me know in the chat, because the… already, I think I have shared that file with you. So just copy-paste the command and be sure that you guys can do the execution of that.
Krish NAik: Okay.
Krish NAik: So just wait. I think I have my… somewhere around this file, I have created that deployment.md file.
Krish NAik: Okay, so, like, this is the high-level…
Krish NAik: flow, but, for now, I think everybody has AWS CLI installed. I think this might be missing in your system. Please do a brew install, this EV stuff, okay? So, this EV CLI requirement is there. So, people can do the installation with pip.
Krish NAik: Or please use, Brew.
Krish NAik: So, preview is also fine, I think. I have used Vue last time, so… for Mac users, please do that, I think.
Krish NAik: Breed.
Krish NAik: Yes, so I think this is the actual package for Mac users.
Krish NAik: Okay, so otherwise, you guys can have a check for Windows requirement.
Krish NAik: Because for Windows, I have not checked that part.
Krish NAik: EVS CLI install.
Krish NAik: Let me see.
Krish NAik: Because this is the main stuff we recommend.
Krish NAik: Git clone, and Python is the other way around.
Krish NAik: Okay, now, I'm sharing this documentation if you guys want to follow, because I feel that
Krish NAik: This part, you guys need to do it, manually from your end.
Krish NAik: Because for Linux-based versions and others, it's much easier. So, I feel that this is much better, doing a pip install AWS EVCLI.
Krish NAik: But if you feel that if you want to do a complete Git clone, and through Python, if you want to do the execution, that is also fine, I have no issue. Whichever way, just be sure you have EV in your system.
Krish NAik: Okay, EB stands for Elastic Beanstalk.
Krish NAik: Okay, so please, follow along. For Mac users, it's much easier. For Windows users, you need to do the installation. So please do have a check on that.
Krish NAik: Okay, for Mac users, again, brew install, as simple as that.
Krish NAik: And once you have done the one, then you can simply do, like, eB-version is the command. eB hyphen hyphen version.
Krish NAik: So you will see something like this. EVCLI with the Python version. So please do the installation, take 2 minutes, 30 minutes, and then let me know, Paul, this part is done.
Krish NAik: Sakesh is asking how to pull the SI have already shared in the GitHub, no?
Krish NAik: You can do a pull, and then simply you can switch your branch, Satish.
Krish NAik: So, everybody please complete the first step.
Krish NAik: Which is installing your EBCLI tool.
Krish NAik: People, for Mac users, much easier. For others, please do that pip install, I think it is much easier. So, according to the original documentation, please do follow according to your operating system.
Krish NAik: Okay? Now, once you have EV, then I hope everybody has AWS, AUWS… okay, this in Project 1 and Project 2 already we have done, so I don't think…
Krish NAik: anybody's system, it will be missing. Then, AWS…
Krish NAik: Okay, so just be sure you have an IAM user. The last IAM user that you have used in Project 2, you can use that, there is no issue.
Krish NAik: So, please do have a check that you are having that.
Krish NAik: Please do have a check on this part.
Krish NAik: Guys, everyone.
Krish NAik: If you don't have, then you have to create a new user, that's why.
Krish NAik: And if you guys… I'm using the old user only, text-to-SQL, right? Because, again, I don't want to do the repetition of the steps.
Krish NAik: But you people can let me know that whether you have a separate one or not.
Krish NAik: Or how many of you have deleted the old IAM user?
Krish NAik: Is there anybody, like, who has deleted?
Krish NAik: the old one, and they will be recreating the new one, and I have to show you exactly the permissions.
Krish NAik: Sanjay is telling good morning, sir.
Krish NAik: Yes, Sanjay, good morning. Someone is asking, do I have to switch to new branch in local and work with the new branch? Yes.
Krish NAik: That's what you have to do so. Because, see, it's not necessary if you want. You can switch and you can get… see, the main purpose I shared, and I've kept it separate, because your main branch is working fine.
Krish NAik: Okay, now, really, I've not done the full testing of this one, so that's why I created a separate branch for that. I hope you get that soon.
Krish NAik: Because it's a bad practice to mix everything in one shot. Later on, you can simply do a merge.
Krish NAik: Okay, but initially, please do the testing in a separate branch. Going forward, like, most of you are… if you are working with AI, so it's a bad practice that, okay, these functionalities are released, always start working in a different branch, and later on, please merge it.
Krish NAik: That's the basic subkit that you learn. Santosh is telling, okay, Sanjay is telling, I missed two classes, how to… if you have missed 2 to 3 classes, that's fine. This project is much easier, Sanjay. There is lesser complexity.
Krish NAik: As compared to Project 2.
Krish NAik: this is a much easier project, we just focus on the core functionality, and right now, today, we are talking about the deployment, and this deployment is also easier. I don't feel it's, like, as…
Krish NAik: tough as compared to Project.
Krish NAik: This is pure Python-focused application.
Krish NAik: Okay, so you can, just go through the videos in 2X. Okay, Sanjay, that's the thing that I will suggest.
Krish NAik: Go for a 1.5x or 2X, and quickly just go through the guest part.
Krish NAik: Santosh, minus RBS IAM. Okay, if you already have an IAM, so let me just, open my AWS account, okay? So, just do it.
Krish NAik: Next to SQL drive.
Krish NAik: Just wait, I think where I have my…
Krish NAik: One, yes, this one. Because even I created a coordinate cluster for now.
Krish NAik: Okay, I think I have been signed out.
Krish NAik: Noted.
Krish NAik: Alright, so these are a few of the things that I have added. Now, these are for my old project also, if you'll see. In this project, you don't need Lambda, guys. So, this one, Administrator Access, AWS Beanstop. This is one that I have added.
Krish NAik: I think, container read-only, this one that I have added, for the
Krish NAik: Later on, we can do it from the CLI also, okay? Just keep it one thing, like admin access and AWS being stock. I think two things are, more than enough.
Krish NAik: Because the strategy will be the same. Doing a local build, then we will push the image to ECR, because I think today's part, manually will be doing it.
Krish NAik: Because CI CD workflows, till now, we have not defined. Once we do the testing, tomorrow we will add that, workflow as a CI.YML file, which will automatically trigger the deployment.
Krish NAik: But first of all, let's do the simple deployment step by step.
Krish NAik: What all to do in AWS right now, just, this is the first step, I am user.
Krish NAik: So, I've just checked Mac, because this is my old project user, so I have other access also.
Krish NAik: Okay, so in your case, if you are doing it, for now, I will say just keep 3 things more than enough.
Krish NAik: Okay, and this access… even I can do it from the command line. I think in your deploy.md file, you have the particular command to do the execution.
Krish NAik: Okay, so just keep these 3 things. Other than that, you don't need Lambda full access, S3 full access. Okay, I think ECR full access, these things are not required.
Krish NAik: Okay, so please, do select, I think.
Krish NAik: You guys, once you do the selection, majorly most of the things will be created.
Krish NAik: MS is telling, I can use the old IAM user, yes, this is my old IAM user only, no? Text to SQL track.
Krish NAik: This is my old user rule. On top of that, just add a few access.
Krish NAik: Actually, you need only one major access, which is this EC2 container. Rest, if you have the admin access, everything, you can do the execution.
Krish NAik: Poonam, is asking… pip install ABS, upgrade user worked for anyone.
Krish NAik: I'm not sure about that, but I think only pip install AWS EBCLI, because even I've not done the testing, so I'm not sure about that.
Krish NAik: People in Windows, please let me know, like, anybody who's using that pip install, AWS EVCLI?
Krish NAik: Because this part… I need someone.
Krish NAik: Like, Abhijit is telling, installed it, showing EV version getting issue. Alright, Abhijit, I will ask you just wait, okay? Let me stop sharing. Abhijit, please raise your hand, because a lot of participants are there from Windows background.
Krish NAik: Just raise your hand, okay, and show it to others. I will ask you to share the screen, okay? Just wait a bit, I will add you to panelist.
Krish NAik: Okay, yes, Poonamja Street.
Krish NAik: Others also, please do refer if you are in…
Krish NAik: Windows, or in Linux-based systems, okay? Please do have a check on this part.
Prusty, Abhijit: Joseph and UV paper. So, Paul, I just installed it now.
Krish NAik: No.
Krish NAik: Just show them that part, that it's working fine from the terminal, just that particular verification.
Krish NAik: So I'm asking Stogart.
Prusty, Abhijit: I use the same command which you said, ubpip install this one.
Krish NAik: UBP install, EBSCLI, no?
Prusty, Abhijit: Yes, that's correct.
Krish NAik: Alright, so Josephine also, UV paper installer,
Krish NAik: AWS EVCLI, I think that is the one.
Krish NAik: Josephine, the same thing. Okay, check that. It's AWS is there.
Krish NAik: Emma, just add, for now.
Krish NAik: AWS Brainstock, just wait, I will show you that screen. Everybody, please let me know that nobody's facing the issue with respect to
Krish NAik: The first part, which is… installing that EVCLI.
Krish NAik: Every one of you, like, should get this in your result, EV-FN version.
Krish NAik: Please do have a check, like, through eb-version.
Krish NAik: Everybody's getting a response, and nobody's getting an error, please do the confirmation in the chat to me.
Krish NAik: Because if this doesn't work, then the next step won't work. So it becomes a bottleneck for everyone. So please be sure this part is working. BB part.
Prusty, Abhijit: Oh, boy, there is a butter here, actually.
Krish NAik: All right. Abhijit, I think you can mute yourself.
Krish NAik: Okay, please do have a check, and these are the major one IAM, people who are asking with respect to IAMs, so just keep admin access for now, EC2 Container Registry. This, I can add it from the… I do have the command in your deploy.md, so you can do a copy-paste, but for now, just keep 3 things.
Krish NAik: If you want the names, I will just parse the names in chat so that you guys can copy-paste it.
Krish NAik: Okay, so this is Juan.
Krish NAik: Then, the Beamstock admin access.
Krish NAik: Beamshook actually launches a lot of services, and Admin Access, I think everybody knows about that, okay?
Krish NAik: MS and others, whoever were asking with respect to IAM, please do have a check that, yes, these are the only things that I require.
Krish NAik: I don't think anything else… Dead.
Krish NAik: Okay, so the first part, once you have done it.
Krish NAik: So, I think, please let me know, the EB part is done, can I proceed ahead, guys? Because I need a confirmation.
Krish NAik: Please provide the confirmation that everything is working.
Krish NAik: not for me, exactly, like, dependency issue and installation failed. Working on it, we are work… why are you using pink log? It's just another service, Gagandip.
Krish NAik: as I told you, majorly 5 AWS services that we are right now using. Okay, so Beanstalk is another service, which is easy.
Krish NAik: to work with. We are exploring 5 major AWS services. The same alternatives are available in
Krish NAik: Like, in AppRunner Alternative, you have in your GCP Cloud Run.
Krish NAik: Okay, so similarly in Azure also you have. Everywhere, the same thing happens.
Krish NAik: AWS fail is to understand the AWS basics.
Krish NAik: See, like, for AWS, I suggest please go and take that Stefan Markin course from UTEM. That's really worth that $13.99, Gagandi.
Krish NAik: Because, YouTube playlist, you can check, there are a lot of YouTubers, but, like,
Krish NAik: Specifically, I have DevOps, guys.
Krish NAik: take with Nana out there, but, again, like.
Krish NAik: According to our specific requirement, very less people only for, that.
Krish NAik: In Udemy, Stefan Markham for AWS is famous, anybody can look into that.
Krish NAik: He is the only, like, market leader with respect to AWS in Newton.
Krish NAik: Like, Chris is in data science part, for a few courses, not even for all.
Krish NAik: Alright, so please let me know, guys, that EV part is resolved or not, or do you need more 3 to 5 minutes?
Krish NAik: For others, please do, like, I will wait 2-3 minutes for people who have not solved. In the meantime, what I can do.
Krish NAik: Matthew, few minutes, install OK file. Take a few minutes, I have no issues, because this becomes a bottleneck, if this doesn't work, few things with respect to debugging, like, if you want to check the logs, then the command is there, like EV logs. Okay, so those things won't work. That's the only problem.
Krish NAik: Otherwise, there is no major issue.
Krish NAik: Alright, now, what I will do…
Krish NAik: Let's get back to our Git, I think Varab shared the Git Git.
Krish NAik: Yes, this is my main catalog.
Krish NAik: Alright, now, ev.ignore file is fine, eb.example. In your case, I think most of you have this .env.example file with you. There is no issue with that.
Krish NAik: Dockerfile, already this same Dockerfile that you can, work with. There is no issue with that.
Krish NAik: Okay, I think undeployment.md. Okay. Now, this is the main file that I have shared, guys. See?
Krish NAik: please do the verification step-by-step, because here you have all the commands listed, the AWS version, EV version, Docker version, so these three things are prerequisite to do this deployment, and I think
Krish NAik: most of you have this part, okay? Then comes AWS STS GetCaller Identity to check your AWS user, okay? These things you guys have done already in the last class. Now, coming to build and push the image to ECR.
Krish NAik: Okay
Krish NAik: Because these are, again, repetitive steps that you have done in Project 1, Project 2, Project 3. So, really, nothing, like, new for anyone.
Krish NAik: So, this is the first step, like, to create an ECR repo.
Krish NAik: In the last project, we have done the same stuff.
Krish NAik: Then, log into your AWS, ECR.
Krish NAik: So this is the part with respect to your authentication.
Krish NAik: Okay, and then doing the local build. Now, if you are in Linux or Windows, please don't use this hyphen, hyphen platform. If you are a Mac, M1, M2, okay, then please use this particular build command.
Krish NAik: The rest, everything is fine. I think you guys agree, please let me know.
Krish NAik: Because, really, like, I think… the Phase 1 should… everyone should be comfortable. Please let me know.
Krish NAik: just look into the screen. And people who are resolving that EV CLI issue, you guys can do it, because it's a repetitive step. But please go through, because I don't think anything is new in Phase 1 that we have done it.
Krish NAik: Now, Satish, you are telling Docker-fn version is not working for me. Please start your Docker client. I think everybody has Docker in their system.
Krish NAik: just start your Docker client, that's the bare minimum requirement. If you have Docker in your system, just be sure you, have, like, on. So, in my case, I think my Docker is…
Krish NAik: My Docker is running.
Krish NAik: Please do have a check, guys, because don't say that you don't have Docker.
Krish NAik: Okay, so please, please let me know all these things you guys are familiar with. Please provide a confirmation, yes, I am comfortable with Phase 1.
Krish NAik: Everybody, because, see, the steps repeat, so many times we have done it. In class, we have done debugging in other projects.
Krish NAik: Okay, so I feel that you should be comfortable by this time. The same thing happens in any other cloud, you have to understand.
Krish NAik: the same things. Probably the name of the service will be different.
Krish NAik: In Google, I think it's Google Artefact Registry, they call it. Okay, in Azure, also, like, similar service, the same way you have to do, always log in, and then you have to do the push.
Krish NAik: Yes, yes, please, this… that is the new branch, Rahul. Okay, in that new branch, because right now, I have not done the complete testing of the deployment.
Krish NAik: That's why I kept it as a separate, branch.
Krish NAik: Okay, build is in progress, okay, so please do have a check on the build. This build will take time, but it should not take a lot of time.
Krish NAik: So, what I will do, so in my case, so let me just switch back.
Krish NAik: I will go, and I will delete all my local images for now.
Krish NAik: Because I have already done the build, but let me delete everything.
Krish NAik: I don't think there is a container running. Okay, you can see here, it's pretty much blank.
Krish NAik: Fine, so now I will start with the mean one.
Krish NAik: Cool.
Krish NAik: EB part, guys, have you resolved it? Please let me know. Then I will start with the Docker build part.
Krish NAik: Everybody. So, if you have done this, if you want to do the login of that, the commands are there. Please, you can directly refer from here. Okay, all these commands that you have.
Krish NAik: So, right now, creating the ECR repo, so just be sure you can use the environment variables, you can see $CR repo, or directly pass the name CRAGA, whichever way you want to do it.
Krish NAik: Okay, you can't do it, I have no problem. So, just be sure you have executed this command, and the repo is available. So, if I show you my repo, where is my repo?
Krish NAik: Where is my AWS account, first of all, yes. So, here, the repo… ECR.
Krish NAik: use… please do a confirmation that you have the repo. So for, in my case, like, CRAG app.
Krish NAik: This is written in the command. So, based on that, the image that got created, it will be close to 1448.
Krish NAik: Okay, so you can do the testing, so please execute that particular command of your Docker build.
Krish NAik: Okay, so using this command, you can actually do the build. So, right now.
Krish NAik: I will be doing the Will Just Wait.
Krish NAik: And I think the speed, in my case, I've already tested the build, so it's faster in my case. In your case, I think it should take some amount of time.
Krish NAik: Please do have a check and then let me know. Can you paste the command here? MS?
Krish NAik: The command is there in GitHub. My command will be different, because my AWS account ID and those things are different.
Krish NAik: I hope you get that MS.
Krish NAik: You have this in your deployment.md in the deploy slash aws-b branch. So please check the commands from there.
Krish NAik: Because by this time, see, the main purpose of this Phase 1 is Build a Docker image.
Krish NAik: Okay, and then, like, you can push that image to your, if you are.
Krish NAik: That is the main purpose of this step. And now, you guys, I know this step takes time, but not a lot. I think within 10 to 15 minutes, it should be done for now. Rajat is telling which command to run fast.
Krish NAik: How many of you are following this document? Please let me know in the chat, first of all. I've given you the document, then also people are asking what to do. Next.
Krish NAik: Please let me know. How many of you have opened this Markdown file in a separate tab in your browser?
Krish NAik: Yes or no? At least tell me that. If you have opened it, the first thing is create the ECR repo.
Krish NAik: If you guys have done the login and the verification, the next step is creating the repo. You can copy this command and paste it. This is the first step, everyone.
Krish NAik: Whoever has missed it. Okay, so you have to do this particular command, and here, you have AWS region. Please change that region to AWS-East 1.
Krish NAik: Okay.
Krish NAik: Once you have done this, here, pass the name. In my case, for example, I've given CRAG,
Krish NAik: rag, or something like this. Okay, now these variables are available, so please do have a check from
Krish NAik: Here, I think.
Krish NAik: Okay, so here, the variables are defined. So according to those variables, please do an update, and if you are using a different region.
Krish NAik: Please take care of that.
Krish NAik: I am using US East 1, others if you guys are changing.
Krish NAik: Because so many times I've done this step, so this is the first step. Once you have this ECR repo, then you can actually start doing the build. Because for your build, you need this ECR report direct.
Krish NAik: image name that I'm giving, so I don't need a tag directly, I can start the push. That is the benefit of that. Otherwise, separately, you need to perform a tag operation.
Krish NAik: Professor, please?
Krish NAik: Follow the steps. All these steps are done.
Krish NAik: And I've repeated it so many times. And finally, we'll see that the image is uploaded. So please take your time and do this. All the commands I have given, step by step, please follow it.
Krish NAik: Everybody.
Krish NAik: Now, someone is telling you Docker has to be run from the project folder in Wrap Terminal. Project folder? Yes, I think. You just need to switch the branch. As in my case, like, I am working with my Gitry folder. In your case, it will be with respect to the branch.
Krish NAik: Please, guys, I think you guys can do it by yourself. How many have started doing the Docker build? Please let me know in the chat, with a yes.
Krish NAik: With a yes in the chat.
Krish NAik: Millions started, Raul started, already trying.
Krish NAik: Struck on EV part, Mitesh, alright, solved that part.
Krish NAik: Can I skip it? ES4 now? EB particles, skip it, Methje. There is no issue in that.
Krish NAik: But later on, when I'll be doing that EVC, once you have done, completed your Phase 1, here EV is not required. Okay, from your,
Krish NAik: Okay, this is Phase 2 also, you are attaching the policy, not required.
Krish NAik: Then comes your, this, from Phase 4 EV is required mutation. Okay, so, like, from this is the main part.
Krish NAik: So, so till phase 1, phase 2, and really in phase 1, 2, and 3, it's really easy. It's just copy-paste that command. And in phase 3, you have to manually update your, docker run AWS JSON file.
Krish NAik: I think, it will be having my AWS account ID, you have to update based on use. So I'll be showing you that change, but first of all, please complete Phase 1.
Krish NAik: If your phase one is not done, then actually, like, if the image is not available, and if you directly try to execute this command, like EV init cirragapp.
Krish NAik: Okay, it will fail. That's why. Like, initialization will happen when you try to create the instance, then it will fail.
Krish NAik: So, just be sure you have the image available in your environment.
Krish NAik: Okay, and I think the size of the image will be close to, like, 1448.83 only.
Krish NAik: Less than 1.5GB, so please do the verification, and then let me know that, yes, the image is available.
Krish NAik: Started the Docker build, okay, alright, fine.
Krish NAik: And people who are having the problem with TB, phase one of…
Krish NAik: Like, from Phase 4, the problem starts.
Krish NAik: So, take your time, and see.
Krish NAik: Started the Dockerfile all right.
Krish NAik: In the Docker file, you don't have to change anything. I think, majorly, I think I have kept it optimized only.
Krish NAik: My previous build was very big. It was, again, 7GB, with all those GPU parts, but now it worked for me, so please do have a check, because sometimes it works in my system, but in few systems, it can be a problem, so…
Krish NAik: Please do the verification of the entire build as successful or not.
Krish NAik: Alright, how CRAC app image will be showing in your AWS, Satish? First of all, see, in these commands, it's already we have tooled.
Krish NAik: in my AWS, so similarly in your AWS, here I've given ECR repo, what will be the name?
Krish NAik: Once this particular name that you have defined, the next step is to build the image in your local. Once you have successfully built, you have to do what? Tag. So first, do the tagging, and then push that into your DCR report.
Krish NAik: then automatically you will see that your local Docker image is available in UCR. Those are the steps.
Krish NAik: These steps are repeated. I feel that in Project 1 also, we have followed these steps. Project 2 also, we have followed this step. Project 3 also, we have followed these steps.
Krish NAik: So please do that, and then we will see with respect to the gun part.
Krish NAik: Let me just open item somewhere.
Krish NAik: Once phase one is successfully done, you guys can let me know, then I will move ahead with the next phases.
Krish NAik: Anything else? No, no, nothing else that I'll be discussing. Because I think next class, that, automation part, then we can actually focus on, because even, like, I'm not sure that, but I know people will be getting a lot of errors. So, it is all being errors and other stuff, Lakshmi, will take time.
Krish NAik: So if you are actually looking to skip this part, then I think
Krish NAik: Next class, or next to next, once we have completed this, we'll be starting cell… like, GraphRack.
Krish NAik: I'm getting AvaWearer. Ava bearer that you have is,
Krish NAik: Please do have a check with respect. Okay, now, please have a check that you have the UV lock file or not. If you don't have the UV lock file, you might get an error. Everybody.
Krish NAik: UV lock file is required.
Krish NAik: Because my Python version exactly that I have provided, I hope it is in your system also. So…
Krish NAik: So, we touch it. Yes, you touch it, like, here. I think… what else is here?
Krish NAik: So, see, let me just show you.
Krish NAik: So, when I've shared that in that particular branch, I think you will be having, because this file, I don't commit, but in your case, this file should be available. If it is missing, then you'll be getting that error, because in the Docker file, if you check, okay, if I show you the Docker file.
Krish NAik: DDDD, yes, this is the Dockerfile. In this Dockerfile, you actually copy this file.
Krish NAik: CopyUV.log. So, if it is missing in your system, you will get an error, as simple as that.
Krish NAik: Okay, so just be sure you have that, and I think everybody knows how to create it in the last class. Through an UV sync, also, when you do it, it gets create.
Krish NAik: Because, right now, even I've added the command to create the UV.log file through this touch, as you can see here, but automatically it gets created even if you do an UV sync. So, in your local part, just see here, because later on, this will be updated.
Krish NAik: Based on the VIL links that you have.
Krish NAik: No, no, no, no, see, this command, if you are Windows and… Like, Linux.
Krish NAik: Please don't add this hyphen hyphen platform.
Krish NAik: By default, it picks up Linux slash AMD64 only.
Krish NAik: But for MacGyles only, you need to pass this platform.
Krish NAik: Okay, Abhishey.
Krish NAik: By this time, I think you guys should be clear, because what is the default one in Apple's silicon chips? What is the platform that gets automatically picked up if you don't pass this parameter?
Krish NAik: Yes, what is the parameter?
Krish NAik: If you don't pass hyphen hyphen platform, then what is the problem in…
Krish NAik: in MAC that you generally face.
Krish NAik: Quickly, let me know what is the default platform in Macs.
Krish NAik: Guys, in the last class, we discussed about this.
Krish NAik: It will be ARM, always remember that.
Krish NAik: Alright.
Krish NAik: Okay, build is done. Build is done, that is spent, then try to push that to ECR. All those things, please do it.
Krish NAik: If you want to do the testing locally, you can do that.
Krish NAik: once the Docker part is done, please let me know, I think,
Krish NAik: This is done, setting up new people…
Krish NAik: Once you guys have done and pushed the image.
Krish NAik: Till that part, once it is done, please let me know.
Krish NAik: Then we will start ahead with the next phase.
Krish NAik: Image pushed, Vishal, good work.
Krish NAik: Okay, now, just tell me, because I think in deploy.md, I haven't added any commands to do a local testing. But if you guys want to do a local testing, then how many of you can do it? Please let me know.
Krish NAik: Because this part, I have not added it, but how many of you can do it?
Krish NAik: Yes, yes, yes.
Krish NAik: C.
Krish NAik: usually if I try to say somewhere, the commands will be there. But a rough, thing that I am telling you, okay, for now.
Krish NAik: Because, you guys have already done the testing, which is it, I think, somewhere.
Krish NAik: For Mac users also, like,
Krish NAik: I think one is the build part.
Krish NAik: For a build, you don't need to do.
Krish NAik: So, this build, I think everybody of you have done it. Okay, now comes running the…
Krish NAik: Mmm, currently.
Krish NAik: So, right now, with respect to executing your main container, this will be your main file. Do the testing, because even, like, I've not done it from my end, but you guys can do it. So, everything will be fine, docker run. Okay, then, defining your port number.
Krish NAik: Okay, then comes your environment variable file.
Krish NAik: So, if you want, I can paste this command in chat also.
Krish NAik: Or I will update it in the deploy.md, or your local testing.
Krish NAik: Because, the environment file, just be sure in that environment file you are passing the correct credentials of Quadrant.
Krish NAik: Alright, because already I have told you in the starting of the session, but again, it's a thing, just take care of that, and just be sure you are not using any localhost stuff.
Krish NAik: Someone was asking error from the registry with the name CRAC. If it's selling does not exist, it means that will not exist.
Krish NAik: Create it, and then only it can be done.
Krish NAik: If it's already created, because the command that you are telling, CRAG app, and then A test, because that name, please check too long.
Krish NAik: Spelling mistake, I can see, some type of…
Krish NAik: Please provide it in, Notion, Abhishek. Alright, I can add it in Notion.
Krish NAik: Mushin, motion, motion, just wait.
Krish NAik: Because these command you guys have already executed for project 1 and Project 2, so…
Krish NAik: I think, recent advanced threat, which is the one. Okay, this is the one.
Krish NAik: Okay, because same on the date of 14th and 15th that I can add it, okay?
Krish NAik: some…
Krish NAik: All right, so I've added it, Abhishek. Okay, if you want to have a check, from there, get it.
Krish NAik: Alright, so… this part, if you have tested it, if the image is available, the next step for,
Krish NAik: students who have already, done the pushing of the image, okay, and if the image is available, let's move ahead with the next step. The next step is, first of all, you have to attach that policy manually. If you have not added, just copy-paste that command. So, where is the command?
Krish NAik: I think in your… Just wait, I think, somewhere.
Krish NAik: Continent not here, where is… which browser? Even I get confused so much, yes. Now, this is the…
Krish NAik: easy to grant, easier full access, okay? You have to just copy-paste this command. In my case, this is already available, so if I open my item… where is my item? Yes, this is…
Krish NAik: If I try to paste it… okay, now, this is the one.
Krish NAik: Okay, so…
Krish NAik: Automatically, you will see that this command will be executed, okay? So, in your case, just be sure, if you have not attached it, just execute this command. Automatically, your Amazon EC2 container registry read-only access will be provided.
Krish NAik: Because manually, also, I told you, if you have done it, it's great. Otherwise, please execute the command.
Krish NAik: whichever way… But do it.
Krish NAik: Alright. Now, once this step is done, now, the next step. Because these are only one-line commands, and instantly you will be getting the responses, there is no wait time.
Krish NAik: Now, okay. Now, coming to updating your docker run.aws.json file, this file I have shared. Now, this will be used by Beamstock for, monitoring your, images in ECR, okay? Now, for this particular monitoring part, please open the file.
Krish NAik: I think this file you have, docker run, docker run, this one.
Krish NAik: Okay, and please update this account ID here, and this is the region. These two things need to be updated. Again, I am repeating, please update this account ID, because this is my account ID that I have shared. It should be your account ID, AWS account ID, the 12-digit number.
Krish NAik: Okay, and then the next thing that you have is, this is the region, in whichever region you are working with. Please pass the correct region.
Krish NAik: Hansia Garav Letters. Now, this is the name that I have been maintaining. If you are giving any different name, please pass that name.
Krish NAik: Okay, so a few simple things that we are just… Following.
Krish NAik: people who are telling Docker image is done, then push that image to ECR. That is the first requirement.
Krish NAik: please update this file, and then let me know that, yes, this part is done. Then I will proceed ahead with the next step, guys. Everyone.
Krish NAik: Because this is a very small change, according… just pass your AWS account ID here, and whichever region that you are working with.
Krish NAik: Docker image done, image push done. Okay, if you guys have pushed the Docker image, then what is the next step?
Krish NAik: please open your Markdown file, okay, and have a look into that, because the same thing, again, I have repeated.
Krish NAik: just see. This deploy.md file, open it in a different, browser, in a different tab, okay, and just copy-paste this command. If you guys have missed it, manually providing the, policy attachment, okay, for that. So, just copy-paste this command.
Krish NAik: If you have done with Phase 2, then comes Phase 3. In Phase 3, you have to do the verification that your account ID, your region, and your main ECR, that one is same one. If something is different, please do change it manually by opening the file.
Krish NAik: I think till Phase 3, it should be done, because then we will start with Phase 4. In Phase 4, you need the package of EP. If you don't have EP package, simply you will get a
Krish NAik: Data.
Krish NAik: Rajat is telling, alright, yes, Amazon EC, yes, the same thing, you have to just copy-paste it.
Krish NAik: still running, okay? It's fine, it's still running. Then wait, see. Don't do the initialization. First of all, everybody, please be sure your image is available and it is pushed to ECR. Once that particular part is done, then only we'll move to the next step, okay? So let's wait. If the image build is not done. We will wait 2 minutes, 30 minutes.
Krish NAik: 1000 seconds, generally, you should not take 1000 seconds, because others…
Krish NAik: For others also. So, Raul, one thing you can check, that during that Docker build, our, NVIDIA libraries and other things are coming.
Krish NAik: just have a check on that, then only we can say. Because others, I think, for everybody, what is the Docker size, please? Can you provide a confirmation in the chat?
Krish NAik: Because it's important.
Krish NAik: If it is taking 1000 seconds, I feel that
Krish NAik: by default, it have picked the GPU version. So, what is the image size? 1.5GB, 1.5GB?
Krish NAik: Okay, because I think, like, the build should be faster for 1.5GB, but, if Dockling is picking up the GPU version, Rahul, okay, it can be a problem, because the script that I have shared, I'm 100% confident that, according to the script, if it is executed.
Krish NAik: it should pick up the CPU version only. So, that's why just have a check on that.
Krish NAik: Rajat is asking, can I share my screen?
Krish NAik: Alright, it's going to be 1028. Alright, I can ask you to share your screen.
Krish NAik: Just wait, I will stop sharing, because small, small issues, let me just have a look once.
Krish NAik: Yes, Rajat, I'm adding you to panelist, okay? Please do have a… please do share your screen.
Krish NAik: And quickly tell me, like, what is the issue that you are facing?
Krish NAik: Image is available, alright, just wait, guys. Let me see it.
Rajat Khanna: Yeah, hi Paul. My screen is visible.
Krish NAik: Yes.
Rajat Khanna: Okay, so I have pushed, the, the build is done, and I have pushed into the, ECR, but it is not coming in the, ECR repository list.
Krish NAik: Open the private repo, huh? Why you are opening your public repo?
Rajat Khanna: I mean…
Krish NAik: by left-hand side, it's written private repo. Below that, there is a repository written. Click on that.
Rajat Khanna: Okay, and I have added the IAM user permission as well, but it is saying, this, I have added this, permission in the IAM user, but it is…
Krish NAik: Show me in the IAM directly. In the UI, just show me that, but if you have added it, it should be coming. I don't think any error. That's a simple attach policy directly.
Krish NAik: If it's there, then it's fine.
Krish NAik: So, just have a check.
Krish NAik: Click on the user, and quickly show me that,
Krish NAik: ACR container read only, it's there. Leave it, I think. This is the one, actually, that you are passing it manually from the… here it's available. Nothing to worry about.
Rajat Khanna: Okay.
Krish NAik: Okay, because, the rule name is, this one policy with…
Krish NAik: Because no such entity, when calling the attach, the rule with the series being stuck, cannot be found. Cannot be found.
Krish NAik: Because if the rule is not created.
Krish NAik: Then, manually, do you need to create the rule also? Because, see, here, I think, in my case, the rule…
Krish NAik: I feel that the rule was not created.
Krish NAik: Rahul is telling how to check the NVIDIA GPU image.
Krish NAik: NVIDIA GPU image, like, in my Docker code, by default, I'm using the local backend.
Krish NAik: Okay, in that local backend, I have kept it, so I think… just wait.
Krish NAik: For that particular check, you can, look into your Docker file.
Krish NAik: in the Docker file, I think…
Rajat Khanna: Just wait. I think it's picking up from pyproject.2ml.
Krish NAik: Where ispy project.2ml file, yes, this one.
Rajat Khanna: And, why, Paul, these
Rajat Khanna: Humanities are getting added, like, a duplicate of this.
Krish NAik: Which one?
Rajat Khanna: This one. So, we have created some tag app, so now the latest image is, there, with the size, and also…
Krish NAik: Again, this letter should be image, it should not be an image index. Please do that verification, because I feel there is some issue, it should not be image index.
Rajat Khanna: And, with the image name, the same file is there, but the name is not there. It's empty.
Krish NAik: Cause, like, I'm not sure exactly. Have you done the tagging?
Rajat Khanna: No, means I directly, run this, Docker push ECR name.
Krish NAik: then it is fine, because the same thing that I have done, but it should be that, image, it should not be a…
Krish NAik: that one, because if you do this later on, I don't think it will be recognized by your, pool.
Krish NAik: When it will be pulling it from the ECR in EC2.
Krish NAik: in… because… This image index.
Krish NAik: Just wait. I think it is creating image index.
Krish NAik: For me, it's showing image, so I think it should be image only.
Rajat Khanna: And also, for you, only 1 entry is there, but for me, it is 3 entries, with 2, 1481, that size is.
Krish NAik: Because it should be same, just you have to push. How many are getting, like, 3 different entries? Please let me know.
Krish NAik: Because I have just pushed a single image only, there is nothing. Otherwise, I can show you by, again, pushing it once.
Krish NAik: I have no issues in that, but I think it should be a single one only.
Krish NAik: You are also getting 3 entries? Alright, let me do it in front of you.
Krish NAik: Because if you feel I've done something different, it's better to do the verification right now.
Krish NAik: Just wait. So first of all.
Krish NAik: Let me delete it, okay? From my ACR, I will just delete it.
Rajat Khanna: You need to share your screen, Paul.
Krish NAik: Okay, alright, fine, I will share.
Rajat Khanna: I will stop my sponsor.
Krish NAik: So, right now, as you can see, I have manually deleted the image, okay? And this particular image is available in my local machine, so I will just try to push it.
Krish NAik: Or if I… if you want me to do the build again, okay, so that part, I can actually do it again, just wait.
Krish NAik: I think this part… let me… okay, so the image is available. I just need to do a doctor push. Okay, and this is the mean that ECR
Krish NAik: repo, entire thing. I know that.
Krish NAik: If you want to do the verification, I think it should be a single one only with respect to the push.
Krish NAik: Let me see once.
Krish NAik: Again, it will take some time. Most of the layers are already available.
Krish NAik: But, should it be a single push, I think it should not be, the Docker one, so…
Krish NAik: All right.
Krish NAik: Okay, so let me just try to do a reload.
Krish NAik: Yes, this is a single image only.
Krish NAik: others, please check and let me know. For everybody, like, 3 things are coming.
Krish NAik: Because, ideally, you don't need to do the tag, it totally depends upon how you are building the image. If your Docker build command is having this entire thing.
Krish NAik: Okay, then actually, like, it is not required with respect to tagging.
Krish NAik: So, the tagging process, I've not done it, directly I've done the pushing.
Krish NAik: So, please do have a check and then let me know. Because right now, I just, did it.
Krish NAik: In front of you. I deleted it, and manually I pushed it.
Krish NAik: So please do have a check on this one.
Krish NAik: Well, it should be an image, rather than an image and text.
Krish NAik: For the image index issue, then we need to debug that issue exactly, like, why that index is coming.
Krish NAik: Okay, so let me know in the chat. According to that, we will take the next steps.
Krish NAik: For me, it's single only, Abhishek is telling all right. Now, that's why, like, few people are telling I'm getting 3 NDs, and few people are telling I'm having. Now, this mixed results, it becomes a problem.
Krish NAik: Now, Rahul is telling for me, this is empty. Okay, Rahul, I will come to you, just wait.
Krish NAik: Still, build is going on, so for people for whom the build is going on, just be sure.
Krish NAik: that it's not using NVIDIA-based libraries.
Krish NAik: Okay, if it is using NVIDIA-based libraries, then only the build can be a lot of time, because the size of the build, also, it will be close to 8GB.
Krish NAik: Because with respect to see, can you see here, like, people were asking with respect to how you know, Paul, that this is using.
Rajat Khanna: the CPU build of PyTorse, here I have tooled.
Krish NAik: explicitly.
Krish NAik: Okay, you need to use the CPU only.
Krish NAik: Okay, Mitesh, Rahul, you guys can see this one.
Krish NAik: So I've added this index part manually.
Rajat Khanna: Paul, I have same, done, deletion of the image in the ECR2, done the build again, and, push it again. The same 3 files are getting added, with one being image index.
Krish NAik: Reset.
Krish NAik: No CUDA slash NVIDIA defenses in the container, alright.
Krish NAik: This is fine, because there is… because now it becomes the OS-level stuff, Rajit. Try to debug this, because even I have this in my PyProject.2ml, Raul is telling.
Krish NAik: If you have this, it should not pick up, so please have a check-see. There are two PyProject.2ml files.
Krish NAik: one specific to this, and one, so just wait, I think let me just start sharing my… this one.
Krish NAik: In my main branch, I don't think I have that. Yes. In my… see, in my main branch, nothing is added. With respect to this, the… okay, alright. But in your… so, when you are doing the build, just be sure you are in this branch.
Krish NAik: If you are not using this branch, it becomes a problem, or manually copy-paste this below that.
Krish NAik: So, just check that, because I think that's the only thing that comes in my mind. If it is there, it should be picking up.
Rajat Khanna: No, I'm in this branch only, that AWS EB branch.
Krish NAik: Not for you, I was talking to Rahul.
Krish NAik: Okay, Raul, just check, because I don't think it should be picking up the… because manually, if we have told that, please use the CPU read, that's why.
Krish NAik: Because for everybody, that part is working, so I feel that it should be working for you. I'm in the same branch.
Krish NAik: Other than that, how to override it?
Krish NAik: That's a… Because according to this, this is the solution. Docker push is not working.
Krish NAik: Okay, Mitesh, try the debugging part.
Krish NAik: And what is the size of the image? Please do have a checkmates on that.
Krish NAik: This index image.
Krish NAik: Alright, now, why this index image is coming? Okay, Rajat, now again, just use, share your screen and show me, because again, I have to see that why that is coming.
Krish NAik: 7GB. 7GB means something wrong, Mitesh. It means that I know the GPU-based libraries that are getting used.
Krish NAik: Show me the main screen.
Krish NAik: Okay, so…
Krish NAik: No red flag.
Rajat Khanna: So, I have, done the build again, pushed it again.
Rajat Khanna: And same 3 files were getting added.
Krish NAik: Once you get the solution, then tell me.
Krish NAik: Because even I'm also looking into that image index issue.
Krish NAik: Alright.
Krish NAik: Because I feel there is some issue with respect to that, so… let's see.
Krish NAik: Because generally, that is how it works. That image index is coming because of that, I feel.
Krish NAik: Alright, alright, alright. Now, just tell me, people in Windows and others, how many of you have manually, added that flag of Linux and other things?
Krish NAik: Because that's what, like, the AI part is also telling, when I actually… because when I'm using the Docker build kit, that multi… because of that multi-architecture, it is doing. Okay, and when you are actually, like, you can manually disable it. If you want, I can paste that entire thing directly.
Krish NAik: Okay, so… just wait, let me just copy-paste this one.
Krish NAik: discrete.
Krish NAik: Alright, because Mac people dish, you guys should not get the problem.
Krish NAik: Because I think Murthaza is also on Mac, but manually you can, do that. So just wait, I'm sharing it in Notion.
Krish NAik: I don't feel… but in Windows, manually, if you try to do it in that particular manner, you generally get that error, as it is suggested.
Krish NAik: So just wait. I think I will update Notion, so this is my…
Krish NAik: On the screen 3 just yet, yes.
Krish NAik: Desktop 2, okay, Notion, yes.
Krish NAik: image index issue, I'm just keeping it like this.
Krish NAik: Okay, now, simply. So, whenever you are doing the testing, just be sure in Linux and Mac you are not using, because when you actually manually hardcore this Linux AMD64, this will happen. If you directly want to pass it, so you can, simply
Krish NAik: do it, because the default Docker actually picks that up. So in your dockerconfig.json, you can manually, parse these features. So in… this is the normal way to do it.
Krish NAik: So here you can keep, this particular flag, provenance is equal to false.
Krish NAik: That's only that, one thing that you were looking.
Krish NAik: Okay, so please, this is the main command, this is the actual solution. You don't need to look into other things, just be sure this particular command that you are using.
Krish NAik: Okay, so… I appreciate it in Notion, from there, try to pick it up, test it out, and then let me know.
Krish NAik: This is not for Mac, again, I'm telling. For Mac, there should not be the problem.
Krish NAik: Okay, so please let me know, because this is the manual, a hard-coded way, but again.
Krish NAik: The main thing is, if you manually try to use that platform and platform, then this particular issue comes.
Krish NAik: If for somebody, build is taking 20 minutes, it means that
Krish NAik: the same thing. Rahul, please let me know whether you had a solution.
Rajat Khanna: Paul, as I am on Mac, so, this Docker build platform, do I need to run like this?
Krish NAik: Yes, I think those three things will be detected if,
Krish NAik: By default, it's not getting recognized.
Krish NAik: I still don't have a solution.
Krish NAik: I mean, perfect.
Krish NAik: Because if it's not working, you can test it out. People, okay, and others also, like, more those, try deleting, regenerate, okay, same 3 images. 3 images are getting built, because for multi-build system that we are doing.
Krish NAik: Because this is the latest one, as I can say, because even I have updated my new Docker, okay, so it totally depends upon that.
Krish NAik: Because I think in… based on Blocker Desktop.
Krish NAik: then it is different. Docker client, it will be different.
Krish NAik: So, check that part once.
Krish NAik: I'm trying the provenance flag, yes. Please do have a check on that, and add this f boom also is equal to false, I think. These two are the only two things are there. Check with these two params.
Rajat Khanna: Same thing coming.
Rajat Khanna: volume.
Rajat Khanna: Okay, time machine…
Krish NAik: Show me, because you guys show me, because even I'm not sure exactly what is going on.
Rajat Khanna: Already sharing.
Rajat Khanna: Are you able to see my screen? Yes, I can. Delete all this stuff, delete all this stuff. Delete.
Krish NAik: Yes, delete all, let's see.
Rajat Khanna: Okay.
Krish NAik: No.
Krish NAik: Matthew is telling, but no tags, for two of them. 3 images, 2 upsides, 1GB, and the other one of zero, I think one for the tag.
Krish NAik: Murta is telling docker build, hyphen hyphen platform Linux AMD provenance flagged, true, okay, this is fine, according to your one that you have pushed hyphen hyphen push.
Krish NAik: Provenance is working, Murthoda is telling. So, if it's failing, I know that it is working. Please do have a check, Rajat, you can look into the chat, see if you are in panelists. You can copy-paste that same stuff.
Krish NAik: There is no load that you have added.
Krish NAik: Check my commander tie upshed.
Krish NAik: Okay, others also, please use the one that I've shared in Notion.
Krish NAik: If it is working, okay, then it's great. Share the notion link? The notion is exactly the same one.
Krish NAik: But I would…
Krish NAik: There is no change in the Notion, it's the same Notion link, just check the last date. I think which date is there?
Krish NAik: This is, yes, Project 3, that page is only there.
Krish NAik: I can share the link once again, but it's the same one.
Krish NAik: Now, why this?
Krish NAik: Please do have a check and then let me know.
Krish NAik: It totally depends upon the build kit.
Krish NAik: Already, I think, if you have used that command, at the end of that command, there was…
Krish NAik: push dot, that's why.
Krish NAik: Please do always check on that, okay?
Rajat Khanna: Worked.
Krish NAik: Worked? Fine. Great. Prognus is working? Alright, guys. That's why.
Krish NAik: Alright, GP3, Matthew is telling… GPT says it, single build with two support OCIS. The new architecture, actually, it, picks up that. Because the build kit of Docker works in that way. So, manually, we are actually disabling it.
Krish NAik: Alright.
Krish NAik: back. And others, okay, now, let's look into… we have time, I think 10 minutes, I can look into the issue. Raul, raise your hand, okay? Just why that GPU part is not working, let's see.
Krish NAik: Because I think MS also told my GPU build is taking time.
Krish NAik: What?
Krish NAik: Why it should take time, that, message is telling same here.
Krish NAik: Then, probably the solution is in that particular file only, I know.
Krish NAik: Okay, because manually I have hard-coded it.
Krish NAik: So I thought it should work for everyone.
Krish NAik: All right, Matthews, you disabled it through the environment variable. Alright, Docker build kit is equal to 0, and then pushing it, it's working. Alright, Matthews.
Krish NAik: Alrighty, let's go for a break, okay? I'm switching on the time.
Krish NAik: It's 10.49, let's start from 11. Okay, so let's go for a 10 minutes break. In the meantime, let me look into the issues.
Krish NAik: Alright, now in your case.
Rahul Parihar: I'm in the branch, I… good.
Krish NAik: In the branch, I can see, yes.
Rahul Parihar: And then I use this,
Rahul Parihar: So in my TOML file, I think so I have this…
Krish NAik: Alright, you have already mentioned this one.
Rahul Parihar: And then I debuted.
Krish NAik: Torch, Torch Vision, both the things are available. Torch CPU, Torch CPU, Torch CPU, alright.
Rahul Parihar: So it is stuck here, you know, building in this path.
Krish NAik: No, this is executing the command, this is different.
Rahul Parihar: Thank you.
Rahul Parihar: But, you know…
Krish NAik: No, that's a verification, that whether the sentence transform was because of that local re-ranking.
Krish NAik: I have added that test, whether it works or not. If it fails, I know that my re-ranking module won't work.
Rahul Parihar: Yeah.
Krish NAik: That's why…
Rahul Parihar: This goes to, like, 1300, 1500, and it never completes.
Krish NAik: Comment that line, then. Manually, comment that line. Later on, we will do the verification. Manually, then comment. Stop the build.
Krish NAik: Remove that.
Krish NAik: better if it is actually creating an issue. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Go to your Dockerfile? Docker file?
Krish NAik: And there, you have that UV run command.
Krish NAik: Yes, go below, go below, go below.
Krish NAik: That line number 35, 36, 37.
Krish NAik: Okay? Comment this entire 3 lines, 3 lines, and below also check if there are any other entries for this sentence transformer check.
Krish NAik: I don't think it will be there, but I have a checkmark.
Krish NAik: Okay, so… workers 1 and 5. Okay, alright, fine. Do the… do the builder now, check.
Krish NAik: What was the use of this sentence transformer? That is the read anchor model.
Rahul Parihar: Real income, go ahead.
Krish NAik: Yeah, mathematical meeting.
Krish NAik: Actually, like, if you're working with that watch re-ranker, okay.
Krish NAik: Save the file, I think, because of that, it's not ideal.
Krish NAik: Okay, then try to execute it once again.
Krish NAik: Others, also, please have a check, on that one.
Rahul Parihar: Opens, execute again.
Krish NAik: Yeah, exactly, no issue then.
Krish NAik: Hmm, wait, it will take some time.
Krish NAik: others, like, Mitesh, you… Also, have a check on that one.
Krish NAik: Because, even for you, just always check that in which part it got stuck.
Krish NAik: Okay, at any point of time, you feel that this part is staying time, and if it is not…
Krish NAik: Required so much. Skip that part.
Krish NAik: Because I feel if there is some type of import issue, yes.
Krish NAik: It can be a problem.
Krish NAik: So, exporting to layers, I think the next step, you can push it now.
Krish NAik: It will be a smaller image.
Krish NAik: do the verification.
Krish NAik: Or try to push it, and according to that, you can test.
Rahul Parihar: Hmm… So you remember, paul, you send one AWS infrastructure project, which was…
Rahul Parihar: So, in order to do that,
Rahul Parihar: You know, I have used Cloud to do that.
Rahul Parihar: within a VPC, you know, setting up the entire, you know, infrastructure… In a private… Subnet.
Krish NAik: Alright.
Rahul Parihar: So the problem is,
Rahul Parihar: the… some of the re… some of the code model or re-ranking models doesn't work. When I say re-ranking, it's like…
Rahul Parihar: I'm obviously using Titan embedding.
Rahul Parihar: You know.
Krish NAik: Alright, AWS from AWS only.
Krish NAik: Okay.
Krish NAik: I mean, the Read Anchor model is there, because I have not used the Read Anchor model from Bedrock anytime.
Krish NAik: Is there any direct model?
Rahul Parihar: Yeah, I was not able to find, yeah, I was not able to find one.
Krish NAik: Because even I have not used any re-ranker model directly from Bedrock, others can also let me know. Anybody has used any re-ranker model which is available?
Krish NAik: Because I know in Marketplace, if I go and attach a service, it's a different thing, but a direct, re-ranking model is available. Nobody has used.
Rahul Parihar: It's pushing, right, so this is working.
Krish NAik: that's working.
Krish NAik: Alright.
Krish NAik: Alright, now, so what is the problem that, like, if the re-anchor, module is not there? So…
Rahul Parihar: Yo.
Rahul Parihar: I think so you have mailed me.
Krish NAik: So, when you're selling image pushing, please check the size of the image. So, if it is taking 10 minutes, it should not take 10 minutes. I feel that it should be having the lesser ones.
Krish NAik: Okay, lesser it should take, I don't think, 10 minutes.
Krish NAik: If your internet speed is slow, then it might take 10 minutes.
Rahul Parihar: So, you mentioned that use, use the S3 event bridge rules.
Rahul Parihar: And then define the step function for… Text extract.
Krish NAik: This is only for your… yes, the data ingestion part, this is.
Krish NAik: Only for data integration, because we keep our vectors directly in S3 only, whenever we are working with, and with that, we use OpenSearch.
Rahul Parihar: Okay.
Rahul Parihar: But you are using, re-ranking optional over here, Bedrock, so…
Krish NAik: Goa re-ranking that, that's one, yes. Because then, manually, I have to host one endpoint through SageMaker for a custom model if I'm going ahead with it.
Krish NAik: If you want to know, so for example, if I want to host my own re-ranking model, then in a SageMaker, I will actually, through Hugging Face, I will create an endpoint URL.
Krish NAik: So that I can hit the ranking one.
Rahul Parihar: Yeah, I'm trying to create a root cause analysis, vector database store where all the…
Rahul Parihar: Projects-related logs and information that the team does as a debugging get stored, you know, and doesn't get…
Rahul Parihar: Push out of the private, you know, network.
Rahul Parihar: And then only used, only use…
Rahul Parihar: Certain bit of solution, which has… which…
Rahul Parihar: the local logs and information stores creates… give you a brief summary of the problem, and then you create that query and pass it to LLM to ask the right, relevant answer, you know?
Rahul Parihar: Okay.
Krish NAik: Right.
Krish NAik: So, in your case, exactly, like…
Krish NAik: what is that? Because I got the IL problem, but exactly, like, what are you looking for?
Rahul Parihar: Evaluation, I don't get the… I get the right, context of the problem statement, but when I pass that context to the LLM, you know.
Rahul Parihar: so it's a legacy application, it's a… it's a COBOL…
Rahul Parihar: Migration to, you know, within a… within a very secure, micro-focused, you know, set of environment, where
Rahul Parihar: system is running only 40% of the utilization of this, ECR containers, where I wanted to use 80 to 85. But there is a certain configuration by the third party, which is not available in
Rahul Parihar: Even in the config… so we wanted to know the configuration part, you know, like, what are the sets of…
Rahul Parihar: how to optimize and utilize the highest CPU boundaries, you know, within the context of the problem.
Rahul Parihar: For even that simple example, If you try to curate.
Rahul Parihar: giving the relevant context. So it's not… one, it is not…
Rahul Parihar: it's not doing a proper, you know, embedding of that solution. I'm not able to explain it properly, you know. It's not giving me the relevant, you know, answer, basically. So I'm trying to do…
Krish NAik: Again, the thing that you were telling, who is doing it, then he or she only can get it. Because even for me also, like, high level, I got it, but again, till the time, actually, I don't deep dive into that, it's very hard to say.
Krish NAik: I think Soham is telling, can I raise my hand? Soham, okay, quickly just show me your part.
Krish NAik: Why you are facing the issue. Raise your hand, Soham. Soham, where are you?
Krish NAik: Yes, I am adding you to panelist.
Krish NAik: It's already 11, quickly just share and then let me know in one minute.
Krish NAik: Amar Sinivas is linked, and you tell me… tell him we have not created anything in PS5, just wait, Amar. Yes.
Soham Dutta: Sir, actually, I've fixed the issue. What was happening, no, if I… in the line… if you… if you share your screen, I can… let me try if I can share my screen.
Krish NAik: You are in panelists, you can't share your screen.
Soham Dutta: Why can't…
Krish NAik: That's twin.
Krish NAik: I will stop, Raul's screen sharing, yes, now, try. Because you are in panelists, I think you should…
Soham Dutta: public.
Krish NAik: Oh, yeah.
Krish NAik: Check?
Krish NAik: Because I have switched on the option, multiple panelists can share simultaneously.
Soham Dutta: I can actually see now.
Soham Dutta: So, if you're able to see my screen… So, if you see, no,
Soham Dutta: what I was creating… so this was… I just modified this course, this line of code. I put a curly braces. If I was not putting a curly braces, no, with course, it was… this LA was somehow getting, truncated.
Krish NAik: Nick.
Krish NAik: I'm not sure, because, see, now this is a variable, if you manually hard-code the entire variable there, that also works, that's why.
Soham Dutta: I was trying with both, like, manually hard-coding was working, but I was trying to use the variable, so if I'm using the variable, it was, like, this part,
Soham Dutta: In this case, I just put a curly bristle under quotes. It was sticking as one continuous.
Krish NAik: Okay.
Soham Dutta: Correct.
Soham Dutta: Alright, so that Kali braces, go back and show me, then I will update it and push it. So everywhere I've just put Kali braces, it's now working. I just use Cloud to actually get what is the correct syntax.
Krish NAik: Alright, alright, fine. This is fine.
Krish NAik: Okay, calibration is on top of every variable you are telling at that part.
Soham Dutta: Yes, yes, it was… Who's handling this.
Krish NAik: link.
Krish NAik: And every variable, fine.
Krish NAik: Okay. Paul Advology. I will add that part in my new comment.
Krish NAik: Alright, so for everybody, I think this… the first part is done.
Krish NAik: I think right now, you don't have… we don't have a rule, I think, because of that.
Krish NAik: If you get that particular problem.
Krish NAik: Okay, so, Rahul, don't worry. I think if we don't have the rule, we'll be getting that particular part.
Krish NAik: To just tweet.
Krish NAik: Both.
Krish NAik: EBCLI…
Krish NAik: Okay, so now, according to our deploy, so everybody… okay, I hope the image is available in ECR, so let's go here.
Krish NAik: Because, I think the command that I've given is directly, to attach, because I think for me, the rule was existing for that particular user. But in your case, if the rule is not available, so you can see here, AWS Elastic EC2, this rule.
Krish NAik: Okay, so, alright.
Krish NAik: Alright, so… so, just have it check, otherwise, manually we can add it. Okay? So, just wait, I will update that particular file. Build is still taking time, even after commenting out UV run.
Krish NAik: Now, Balaji, in your case, where the build is taking time. Everybody, please have a check if you have the particular role or not, otherwise you have to create the role.
Krish NAik: Please, have a check and then let me know on that.
Krish NAik: Do you have the rule?
Krish NAik: Otherwise, then again, I have to manually, like, create the command.
Krish NAik: Because someone just within… If you want me to share my entire,
Krish NAik: Command OK, we'll just wait to think.
Krish NAik: I have did it. Hashtag.
Krish NAik: If it is not available in that case only, I'm sure.
Krish NAik: Okay, now, step by step, like, all these commands that you need to execute it.
Krish NAik: Okay, now this is the first command, IAM createRule. I think in the last time also we have gone through, and this is where I'm giving the name of this rule. Okay, now, if this rule is not available, simply the command that I have shared, it won't work. Okay, so please do have a check.
Krish NAik: And then, actually, all the policies, like, if you have that admin access policy for AWS Beamstock, everything will work. Okay, but only the last policy that I have manually added for ECR pool. So I have a check, so this is, like, one way. If you don't have the role, please create the rule.
Krish NAik: Okay, so I have added this part.
Krish NAik: And, please don't copy this create role, part, I am hitting the enter, okay? So this is the first command. If the role is missing, please create it, and then execute that particular command.
Krish NAik: Because if I show again back my IAM, again, I will show you.
Krish NAik: I am… okay. So, I have this administer access AWS Beanstalk. So, if I have this, so manually I don't need to provide
Krish NAik: Other, I can say policies. If I search here Beanstalk, you will see a lot of policies will be shown. Beanstalk.
Krish NAik: Okay, I think, add permission, add policies here.
Krish NAik: being stuck.
Krish NAik: Okay, so there are a few beanstalk policies. Out of this, I'm not using everything, like SNS and other things are not required in my case.
Krish NAik: So, very specifically, like, if you want to pick up the exact ones for that, you can select one by one. Like, Beanstalk, web tire, Worker Tire, okay, multi-container, and a few other things. But I will say, please keep it, it is not required.
Krish NAik: For you, only this is required, and I think the EC2 rule. These two are the major ones. Other than that, I don't feel any other is required. Okay? So, first of all, please recreate the role. Once the role is created, please attach the policies.
Krish NAik: This, I have given much more granular level policies, but if you are working with admin access, everything will work fine. Okay, so please have a check and then let me know.
Krish NAik: Because this part, I think, please let me know whether it's working or not.
Krish NAik: people who were getting the error that rule is not available. So, using the first command, you will be creating the rule. Once the rule is created, you can simply attach this particular, policy for your ECR pool. It's working now? Okay, alright.
Krish NAik: Alright, fine, if it is working, great. Now, in the next step.
Krish NAik: Let's go back to our Docker one, because I think next we'll be doing EB, EB init, for our project creation part, for our beanstalk. Yes, initializing this one, okay.
Krish NAik: Working, working, everybody, if you have given me a confirmation, okay, please let me know about those.
Krish NAik: Because now, this is the part where actually it takes time.
Krish NAik: So, first of all, I'll be initializing one…
Krish NAik: Now, this is the name of my EV service that I'll be creating.
Krish NAik: Okay, so if I show you my UI, so in your UI, if you open your Beamstock… Now, Beamstock is a totally automated service, okay? Now, this is one of the easiest ways. In GCP, how many of you know about App Engine?
Krish NAik: Anybody knows about App Engine?
Krish NAik: There's a service called as Google App Engine. In App Engine, you have two different types of formats. One is the standard engine, one is the flex engine.
Krish NAik: Okay, so generally, like,
Krish NAik: There, you can directly upload a zip file, and you can do the deployment, a very similar strategy here also that you have.
Krish NAik: Okay?
Krish NAik: But, I will say Beanstalk has much more added features, because it actually launches the entire CloudFormation stack.
Krish NAik: Okay, whereas Google App Engine, does not.
Krish NAik: If you are doing it in Flex, then again, it does to a certain extent, but again, not an entire stack.
Krish NAik: Alright, you will see something like this, an environment with respect to, like, applications. Okay, now, this is my old one.
Krish NAik: I think somewhere around.
Krish NAik: Because even I have not tested it, but later on I will test at whether this part works or not.
Krish NAik: So, you will see something like this. So, for the first step, please follow along the command. First of all, just, create, like, eB initCRAG, okay? So, please do, pass this as a… if you have a variable, or pass US East 1, according to that.
Krish NAik: Okay, so if I try to do it from my end, I will go back to my terminal.
Krish NAik: Yes, so I will paste it here.
Krish NAik: U.S. East, click on one.
Krish NAik: Then comes Docker running platform, this is fine. Here, I'm just writing one more pre for now, because I already have a new one.
Krish NAik: So, first of all, the initialization, I will hit enter. The initialization will take place.
Krish NAik: Then in the next step, you can see application.
Krish NAik: like, CRAG app has been created.
Krish NAik: Okay, so in your case, also, you should not get any type of error in this step. In the next step, the main error comes.
Krish NAik: which is where, like, the initialization, you can see, dot, this beanstalk slash config.yml will be created. So right now, there are two options.
Krish NAik: So generally, right now, I don't need any separate type of load balancer and others.
Krish NAik: Okay, now this is a costly service, as you can see, like, roughly around it will come close to $40-$50, because a lot of other service, like EC2, will be getting launched in EC2. I'm selecting a T3.large, with an 8GB RAM, at least, because mine…
Krish NAik: I know that it can work with a medium also, but for, right now, just for a safety check, I am using T3Large. Now, if you want load balancing with auto-scaling, then you don't need to pass this hyphen hyphen single parameter. Single refers for a single instance, and if you don't pass this.
Krish NAik: the entire thing with load balancer and auto-scaling will take place. Please don't do this one, this is a much costlier one. For our initial learning, this is fine.
Krish NAik: Okay, so I will just copy this stuff.
Krish NAik: And then I will go back and let's see what happens here.
Krish NAik: Alright, so… Let me add one more P there.
Krish NAik: Now, this process will take time. If any error happens, then again, I have to delete it, and again, re-initialize it. So, a lot of things happen, so let's wait and see.
Krish NAik: Viraj is telling, in my case, around 6.5GB docker image got created. Viraj, the main thing that you have to debug is that dockling is not picking up the CPU bit. That is the main issue that you have.
Krish NAik: Okay, so please have a check on that and try to debug people for whoever, like, that GPU part is not working, it means that your email size is bigger. It means that Dockling is using the bigger one. Okay, so manually I have added it in PyProject.2ml.
Krish NAik: But again, please have it checked, and that's the only thing that you need to debug in your application.
Krish NAik: Okay, it will take some time. In the meantime, let me see my application.
Krish NAik: This is my older ones.
Krish NAik: And automatically, we'll see that other, services are also… it will be launched.
Krish NAik: Because, really, I have not debugged this deployment entirely.
Krish NAik: But, right now, let me see with respect to EC2, what are the… instances…
Krish NAik: Why? This is just an instance. Generally, like, take your decision, it can be medium also.
Krish NAik: I'm taking an 8GB one, you can take a smaller one according to your application.
Krish NAik: Yes, it will be.
Krish NAik: Take a smaller one. For sentence transformers and other things, it's better to go with an 8GB RAM. I feel it's safer, but if it works previously, like, 4GB also works. I know there are no issues in that.
Krish NAik: Let me see, like, why I'm getting this so bad wave one here.
Krish NAik: like, Nginx as my main load balancer, the default one.
Krish NAik: Okay, waiting for EC2 instances to launch. Alright, let's see.
Krish NAik: In your case also, it will take time, but again, like, deleting also, it takes time. Creating also, it takes time.
Krish NAik: If you get any error, then manually, like, we can do that.
Krish NAik: So I think if there is some issue with respect to that.
Krish NAik: Alright, I think the container port, one mistake if I try to… Just sweet.
Krish NAik: 1… mistake, I think, that I have in mind.
Krish NAik: Docker and EWS, okay, there… I think the host port that I am using is 800.
Krish NAik: I think, that needs to be done, and later on, I have to update my environment variable, because our application doesn't have any type of environment variable that also we need to update it.
Krish NAik: Let's pause that stuff, just wait once.
Krish NAik: Okay, two things we'll be updating, but in the meantime, just, have a check, with respect to the, like, are you getting some, like, instance deployment completed successfully, something like that?
Krish NAik: Please let me know. Because right now, in this particular environment, we don't have anything.
Krish NAik: How many of you are getting this? Because automatically, it will complete all the events, so just wait for the entire execution to be completed. It takes around 4-5 minutes.
Krish NAik: What will be the cleanup command?
Krish NAik: Why instance? Okay, already 12 million?
Krish NAik: BB.
Krish NAik: In EV also, I'll be… You have the command.
Krish NAik: After running all the command, I should see in console Wingstop. In here, there also you can look into, there is no problem, but you will see something like this.
Krish NAik: Okay, so please do have a check on the part, like, how many of you… are you getting any error or not? Because if there is an error, then, like, again, deleting the stack also takes a lot of time, like, just, like, launching the stack.
Krish NAik: Please do have a check, okay? Now, if… how many of you are getting? Because the other commanders, like, through… you can do it, like, EV terminate. You can use that command if you want to delete the entire stack at any point of time.
Krish NAik: Okay, so, for example, if I do this one… I'm just showing you this for now, EB Terminate.
Krish NAik: Okay, can you see? It is asking the environment, C, rag prod, and all associated instance will be terminated. Okay, so it just… because after once you have done it, you have to understand it will start charging. It doesn't matter if the application is up or not.
Krish NAik: Okay, so simply, like, if I… I'm just showing you this step, because, for you, once… if you have created, and if it's working, this is the simple command, terminate.
Krish NAik: Okay? For doing your entire cleanup of your beanstalk. I think who asked it in the chat? Melind asked it. Milind?
Krish NAik: I hope, okay, you can try this command. Rajat is telling it failed, it failed, like, what is the error you are getting? Because it's failing, I want to know exactly the error.
Krish NAik: Site is not reachable, that is fine. We have… we have not added environment variables. Again, the container port, that we need to update. We have… there are a lot of things to update. It's not about executing this one.
Krish NAik: Okay, so I need to check, it's saying that,
Krish NAik: Okay, Rajat's error. This may take a few minutes. Error, instance deployment, details, EV engine lock, the ECF service failed to authenticate here.
Krish NAik: Private repo authentication.
Krish NAik: See, private repo authentication will fail if you have not passed the correct name up in your, this one.
Krish NAik: in your, Docker AWS JSON. If this name is wrong, simply the authentication won't be successful. So whoever is getting that error, please do have a check on that one.
Krish NAik: Ignore, I may be in wrong direction, maybe in wrong directory. Alright, Melind.
Krish NAik: Aye.
Krish NAik: All the service created.
Krish NAik: Right now, you are telling, Amar, AWS billing came $11, should we terminate all services?
Krish NAik: created previous EC2 containers, this means…
Krish NAik: $11 right now you got charged. I don't think $11 right now you won't be getting charged.
Krish NAik: How much?
Krish NAik: If you have some services on from our previous project, you might get charged. Because even for me, the billing for this month was less only, like, 200 rupees or 300 Indian rupees.
Krish NAik: Okay, and this account is dedicated only to this batch, no other batch I'm doing it.
Krish NAik: Yes, yes, turn off every project and other things. Just…
Krish NAik: clean everything, there should not be anything, because you can keep only the IAM user, that is the only thing I suggest.
Krish NAik: Okay, if this is wrong, you will be getting an error. Alright. Now, already I've done the termination, but again, I'll be doing a complete relaunch, just wait.
Krish NAik: Alright, waiting for EC2 again to delete.
Krish NAik: Just wait, like, step by step, again, I need to follow. Few things that I'll be doing.
Krish NAik: My kid…
Krish NAik: Actually, in your Docker and AWS, there will be one option of host port. Okay, remove that line of host port.
Krish NAik: Because my container port is 8000, okay? And because of that host put, you are getting the nginx error. That is the first error that we need to debug. Then we need to add environment variables, okay? So, step by step, let's do. For your environment variables, I think I have already added the command. Please make that command ready.
Krish NAik: Okay, so… open your Docker file.
Krish NAik: Where is Docker if I just wait? Yes.
Krish NAik: In your docker.md, I think here.
Krish NAik: docker.md. Deploy.md, sorry.
Krish NAik: Deploy.md, deploy.md, deploy.md…
Krish NAik: Alright, so over here, can you see that, once we have the environment created, the next step is basically to set up. So you have to manually pass all the environment variables.
Krish NAik: Okay, so you have to make this command ready for that. Okay, so according to that, don't use double quotes, directly pass those keys, and you need to execute it.
Krish NAik: Everybody, please be sure that, if this is successful, in my case.
Krish NAik: Just wait, I will delete all the environments and others.
Krish NAik: Any other thing that I need to do, I think EP terminate is done.
Krish NAik: Let me just, relaunch this one. Okay, just wait.
Krish NAik: Raul is, telling error, deployment fail, instance deployment fail, EV engine log, alright. It's telling, the operation.
Krish NAik: Create environment is complete without any errors.
Krish NAik: B…
Krish NAik: Guys, just have a check with respect to the policies, okay? If this policy is missing, then pulling the image from ECR will fail. So, if I show you…
Krish NAik: Okay, so where is that, policy that I've added?
Krish NAik: Just wait.
Krish NAik: Yes… If this particular policy is missing from you.
Krish NAik: this, Amazon EC2 Container Registry Read Only. If this is missing, you will be getting the error. Now, I feel when I look into the error, Rajat and others also can confirm, Rajat, your previous error got resolved.
Krish NAik: Instance deployment failed to download the Docker image. Can you see here how… so I feel when you are unable to download the Docker image, there is an issue with respect to this EC2 container registry access.
Krish NAik: Okay, so just try to execute this particular command again, and then, try.
Rahul Parihar: So, I have this execution… executed command.
Rahul Parihar: Available.
Rahul Parihar: I did…
Krish NAik: if you have executed, just have a check, because I feel then there is nothing other. This is, if instance deployment failed to download the Docker image.
Krish NAik: Because then this is Container Registry stuff only.
Rahul Parihar: You know, the…
Krish NAik: I have done and terminated it.
Krish NAik: Just have a check on that one, because I think if you have executed, try to re-execute it.
Krish NAik: If you have terminated, Rajat, you can create it. Whenever you are creating, just be sure you are actually doing that.
Krish NAik: Otherwise, it will become a problem.
Krish NAik: Okay, so, like, if I go from the UI part, because I'm actually deleting stuff, once this entire deletion is done, I will start from scratch.
Krish NAik: Okay.
Krish NAik: So, I think, my environment…
Krish NAik: Know the name, do I need to run… no. If you have done the termination, you can use the same name. But if you have not done… not done the termination, Rajat, you can't use the same name.
Krish NAik: Right now, I think the termination of my environment is taking place, so I will just do it.
Krish NAik: And… because this is the actual rule that I have created and am currently working with.
Krish NAik: Let me wait for this one.
Krish NAik: Others, like, I have shown you the termination part, but…
Krish NAik: If you have done it, because successfully, like, this should be the lock, like, successfully launched environment, and whatever the name of the environment that you are passing.
Krish NAik: Huh, so I think…
Krish NAik: Now I think I can actually create one more. Now I will start. We create single. Shall I remove the host entry from docker run? Yes, remove the host entry. Like, if you check my entry, now I have actually removed that.
Krish NAik: Okay, so… There is no problem with that.
Krish NAik: I'm sharing the update also with you guys.
Krish NAik: This is the EDF file, actually.
Krish NAik: push the recent change. I have just added, removed the default NGINX port, which is 80 by default. Okay.
Krish NAik: Registering in Docker, in Docker was 5. If you see CRAG app, it's written.
Krish NAik: In Dockerfile, it's very specifically written, let me check once, because this is the ACR repo part, there is nothing. Now, you are telling that in Docker… in Docker was file, if you see, CRAG app name is already written. In Docker, alright, let me check in Docker, you are telling this is already written.
Krish NAik: Just wait.
Krish NAik: Because I don't think there is any problem with respect to this particular file. There is no such entry, Rajat. Please have a check.
Krish NAik: Okay, because your EV commands are not related to that.
Krish NAik: Alright, now I will start creating. Everyone, see, please focus on, right now, I will start creating it from scratch, so let me…
Krish NAik: Just… Create the first service.
Krish NAik: Okay, now, just wait, Rajat, you were telling, add me.
Krish NAik: Yes, others, please have a check on that.
Krish NAik: Raise your hand, Rajat.
Krish NAik: Yeah, Rajitan. What you were telling, that in command, it's in deploy rag mode, what is that?
Rajat Khanna: Yeah, so, in the, one minute… in the, deployer.md file, in the…
Rajat Khanna: Phase number, 5, create a beanstalk environment. So, it's a eb create CRAG hyphen prod. You were saying name should be same, so in the Docker AWS, it is CRAG hyphen app.
Krish NAik: So, is… Wait, wait, wait, wait. First of all, you are telling he had deploy.md file, the first step, just wait. You are telling in this file, in,
Krish NAik: Where is the deployment.ms? In this file, I have written here, eBay init cirrh, yes.
Krish NAik: After that, what is the next step?
Rajat Khanna: The, phase 5, CRAG hyphen prod, eB create.
Krish NAik: Yes.
Rajat Khanna: Yeah, so, so I have done that CRAG app creation, and after that, I run prod, so the.
Krish NAik: Maintain these names across, same time.
Krish NAik: Just remember that.
Krish NAik: Both the names should be the same, don't use different names.
Rajat Khanna: So if… if in the phase number 4 we are using CRAG app, so in the phase number 5, it should also be CRAG hyphen.
Krish NAik: Yes, then app name should be seen.
Rajat Khanna: Okay, okay, so that's the reason, the previously error came.
Krish NAik: Okay, alright. Don't use different names, then it becomes a problem. Balaji, the Docker image got created sizes 4.5J again, like, GPU issue and that part.
Krish NAik: Now, I can do the manual debugging, you see, like, manually through requirement.txt, I can do it, but as I'm not using, I thought about explicitly mentioning it in UV file.
Krish NAik: Okay, so that part I will do apologize, okay?
Krish NAik: How to correct the GPU issue? Because in my code, we have manually done the hard coding of that.
Krish NAik: The other way around is, like, I think…
Krish NAik: through your uv.log file, I think I need to manually update Duh.
Krish NAik: from where it's getting. So, myuv.log file, if I show you. It becomes actually a manual process.
Rajat Khanna: From here.
Rajat Khanna: Again, Paul, it came with an error.
Krish NAik: If you don't have that policy, simply it will throw an error, whatever you do.
Krish NAik: Because the policy should be up in there. EVCreate, this need to be EVCreate rack app.
Krish NAik: Av create, AVCreate, actually… no, no, no, no, that is the name of the environment. First, you initialize the service, Melind. Then you create the environment.
Krish NAik: That, again, that create part can be different also.
Krish NAik: Inside a single environment, you can have multiple applications.
Krish NAik: But right now, a single, environment with a single app, that's the idea, so I'm telling you the same name. Otherwise, you can create multiple ones.
Krish NAik: So here, if I go to Dockling, okay.
Krish NAik: Hmm…
Krish NAik: Push.
Krish NAik: Anywhere with respect to this.
Krish NAik: Please, let me know for anybody, like, like, this installance deployment completed successfully, how many of you are getting this one?
Krish NAik: Because majorly, it says, can be, and just be sure the IAM users that I am using, everybody is… if something is missing, you might get an error. Again, I'm just showing you all the…
Krish NAik: policies that I am using.
Krish NAik: Because I think only one thing
Krish NAik: Don't use Lambda and other stuff. In this particular process, we are not using Lambda, so that part you're gonna skip. Actually, rag deployment, these two things are not required the last. Other than that, this is the main one.
Krish NAik: So, have a check with this, because I have added EC2 full access. Okay, so… and EC2 container. These two are the major ones. If…
Krish NAik: You can actually, if you have EC2 full access, by default, this comes into the picture. But, please have a check.
Krish NAik: And if in the error, if something is written, like, it cannot download the image. If it cannot download the image, it means that it doesn't have the access to it. And if it doesn't have the access, you need to manually check that.
Krish NAik: Okay, so please have a check with this.
Krish NAik: Everybody. For me, it's failing, trying to fix it. Okay, alright, have a check on that one, because the other way around is, like, removing and with respect to the permission.
Krish NAik: Because, the last three permissions are not required, actually. Majorly, the top 4 are actually the main one. So, if it is failing, please let me know.
Krish NAik: Because once I have this one.
Krish NAik: Then I think remove the host port with respect to the container.
Krish NAik: Just wait, and then again…
Krish NAik: somewhere I will be keeping money.
Krish NAik: Entire file, I think here I have the entire…
Krish NAik: Because there can be one parameter or some type of issue. Okay, so that part. Murthaza, yeah, you do… try to do that debugging step. Because I have a feeling that if you have an admin access majorly, all those things can be done. So, it can be… and what is the exact error?
Krish NAik: Also, have a look into that part.
Krish NAik: Hmm.
Krish NAik: Then delete the previous ones, now we're not passing the key details. Yes, yes, manually you have to do it, Mantaj.
Krish NAik: Because your DAW TV things won't come into the picture.
Krish NAik: And later on, what I will do, this particular command that I've updated, no, later on, I will update that, like, in tomorrow's class in CI, but I will update it from the GitHub Secrets.
Krish NAik: Okay, so that one part, I have updated it.
Krish NAik: No, I think I can… I've updated that particular port, so… I think…
Krish NAik: Once this command execution is done, I will update the application with an EV deploy.
Krish NAik: command. So, let's see whether it works or not, when I'm not… You need to deploy.
Krish NAik: Because this error… I think, immediately, if you have… this is, like, EC2 and ECR.
Krish NAik: these two services, access should be available. If the access is not there.
Krish NAik: You might get, some type of, issue than that.
Krish NAik: Hmm, let me see… Beanstalk, yes, it is there.
Krish NAik: Alright, at least I got something, so for me…
Krish NAik: Later on, we will do it, but at least I can see something from here, so…
Krish NAik: But, that's the main thing, like, updating the first part.
Krish NAik: Because the steps are pretty much simple.
Krish NAik: But, again, with respect to permissions and other stuff, just have a check. Otherwise, you can… because I will stop sharing, and, you guys can let me know.
Krish NAik: No, exactly, because at least I'm getting the main one, Abhisheikh, okay, let's take your one.
Abhishek: Yeah, I promise.
Krish NAik: that I would come to. Yes. You want to share?
Abhishek: Yes.
Krish NAik: I do.
Krish NAik: Yeah, Rajat, for you also. Because that, how many of you are getting the same error that the Docker container cannot… is not downloadable? Please let me know.
Krish NAik: Milinda also raising a hand.
Krish NAik: Because at least I can see that the first step is working, and…
Krish NAik: How, can I know if Beanstalk is created or not?
Krish NAik: You can use the command EV space logs.
Krish NAik: or from your UI also, from AWS console, you can go to VIN stack, and from there, it will show that the service got created or not.
Abhishek: Yeah, so, actually, I'm stuck at this particular point, which is saying creating applications.
Krish NAik: Wait, wait, wait. First time, it actually takes a lot of time. Okay, okay, that's right. Easily wait, because for me, initially, I think first time, I don't know, it took time.
Abhishek: Don't for me, also.
Krish NAik: Not added to screen share.
Krish NAik: I think you can see, because Abhishek's screen, I can see.
Krish NAik: Okay, Rajat, you were telling not added… I have not added it here yet. I will add it just to it. Milint, you also, screen share, please let me know.
milind kulkarni: Gabby, can you hear me?
Krish NAik: Mmm, yes.
milind kulkarni: Okay, let me…
milind kulkarni: I can't share the screen right now, and I don't get an option to share.
Krish NAik: You are not in panelist.
Krish NAik: Everybody, please focus on the first step where you are creating.
milind kulkarni: Good year.
Krish NAik: In creating, if you are getting any errors, you cannot actually move it to the next step. At least that process should be completed. Later on, we will be updating the environment variables and other things. That is fine.
Krish NAik: Here's weapon. At least till the first part, if you see, that is the main thing. Like, once you get, like, if I'm sharing, like, I think it's somewhere, at least check till this point.
Krish NAik: You are getting the application for now.
Krish NAik: I've not added any certificates and others, but later on, you will see something like this. So, from your UI, when you actually go, I think, from this environment, you'll be getting this particular domain. So, try to access that, and can you see the application or not? That is the first step.
Krish NAik: Later on.
Krish NAik: Application-level things we can debug, so please have a check till this point. Yes, now I will stop sharing. Whoever wants to share, please do that million.
milind kulkarni: I'm cheating.
milind kulkarni: So here it's selling.
Krish NAik: See, Elastic S3 bucket, fine. Waiting for EC2 instances to launch, this may take a few minutes. Instance deployment failed. Ev-engine.log, that,
Krish NAik: file will be created, actually, in your system. You can look into that particular folder, okay? Written code, this one is complete, but with errors. For more information, free troubleshooting fine.
milind kulkarni: Are you checking my log? This… that's not a my share, most probably.
milind kulkarni: I'm getting instance deployment head to download the Docker image.
Krish NAik: This error you generally get because of the access part.
Krish NAik: And you people have already executed that access thing.
Krish NAik: At the CR pool, you see two…
Krish NAik: Okay, for safety, see, in Notion, whatever the things that I have pasted, again, I'm repeating, then execute all the steps you are getting, because I think…
Krish NAik: Everything. From starting, have you executed the first one?
milind kulkarni: Yes, I did.
Krish NAik: Okay, for now, just click on EB Terminator. Every step you have executed.
milind kulkarni: Yes, but I can retry.
Krish NAik: just show me one, just delete it and show me. First of all, terminate. EV space terminate. Let's delete and let's see what's there.
Krish NAik: Amar, yes, I will come to you. Amar is telling my upload file 100% an upload file, but error saying invalid parameter value environment CRAG already exists, yes. If it already exists, Amar, you cannot execute the same name.
Krish NAik: You have to change the name of the environment. You can add, like, in proddt, something like that.
Krish NAik: Okay, so just terminate it, okay, and then we will do it from scratch again, just wait.
Krish NAik: Even for you, if you want to delete that existing one, you can use the command EVTERMINATE.
Krish NAik: You can use hyphen hyphen force also, hyphen hyphen all, like, these parameters are common to EV.
Krish NAik: Because at least the application should be up. Then, with respect to other things, we can test it tomorrow.
Krish NAik: But at least, guys, everybody, till this point, at least try to complete it today, that the application should be up.
Rajat Khanna: Paul, can I share now?
Krish NAik: Yes, you can.
milind kulkarni: Yeah, I can… I can, I can stop and come back again.
Krish NAik: Because I need to see that entire process, step by step, everything you have executed.
Krish NAik: I don'.
milind kulkarni: I'll reshare once.
Krish NAik: Just wait once that, thing is done.
Krish NAik: Okay, now here it's telling, EV create, application, alright, uploading, this part is fine, scene name, alright,
Krish NAik: Right now, I don't have anything with respect to domain. This is fine, this is fine, this is fine. And here, it's telling, output engine, the deployment field, the ECR failed to authenticate your private.report.
Rajat Khanna: I have changed… I have done the same name as well. So see if the initiate… init, you can see CRAG, app initiate.
Krish NAik: I can see this one.
Krish NAik: Let me just click… let me see… because your download failed when you're selling the ECR service.
Krish NAik: Failed to authenticate your private repo.
Krish NAik: Okay, so that's why I'm feeling that why this authentication from your EC2, like, when it's trying to actually pull the image, here, the authentication is failing. Okay, just wait.
Krish NAik: That's great.
Krish NAik: We terminate, okay, all the name of the environment, so just wait, let me see in the meantime.
Krish NAik: Okay… Alright, alright guys, I think,
Krish NAik: one problem, okay, that can be there. The instance profile, like, if anybody can actually go back to that motion part.
Krish NAik: Melinda, I'm looking into your screen. Okay, go back to that notion quickly. For everyone, like, whoever is getting that, part.
Krish NAik: First of all, open, because whenever… Yes. And open your, code editor. I think .stop folder that got created.
Krish NAik: Show me that.
Krish NAik: In your local, local. When you do EV init, automatically that folder gets created in your code editor.
Krish NAik: You have not opened, opened in…
milind kulkarni: Yeah, I mean…
Krish NAik: Just… see, dot Beanstalk is there, no?
Krish NAik: Dr. Beanstalk.
milind kulkarni: Okay, sir.
Krish NAik: Yeah, open that folder, there will be a config.yml file. Yes, this one, config.yml. Okay? Now, here, in the instance underscore profile, it is, it is actually equal to null.
Krish NAik: Okay, their pass, the name that we have actually created. I think because of this parameter, okay, it, is creating the issue.
Krish NAik: Instance underscore profile in line number 11.
milind kulkarni: Just pass that your AWS. Go back to that, notion.
Krish NAik: In Notion, that, name is there.
Krish NAik: You have to pass the name of the role, actually, that is the only thing.
Krish NAik: Yes, here, I see instance profile name. In every command, at the last, there is instance profile name, from number 3.
Krish NAik: Can you see instance profile name?
Krish NAik: Below, below, below, below, below, below, one more from 3, yes. Instance profile name is there. Copy that name and pass it there.
Krish NAik: Okay, do one, Ctrl-S, yes.
Krish NAik: Okay? Now, you can simply, like, terminate and try to create that part. If it is terminated last time you have already terminated, okay, then you can try to do the recreate part.
Krish NAik: Because, I think because of that, Murta, you also, like, in config.ml, just update the profile name according to the command, okay, and then try. You can terminate it and then recreate it.
Krish NAik: Everybody, please try that part.
Krish NAik: Because for me, also, like, without that instance profile, it worked, but
Krish NAik: Like, again. Like, I have not done that, but that is the main solution that is being shown. Just wait. Here, it's telling you we create, rag alt write, upload complete, let's see whether that docker is getting pulled or not.
Krish NAik: And, the other way, okay, because two options are there. When you are creating, then directly you can actually pass that particular
Krish NAik: parameter. So, just go back there, millionth, in your terminal.
milind kulkarni: I'm just at…
Krish NAik: Yes, yes, like, I'm adding… Both the things here.
Krish NAik: Because, this is the other way around.
Krish NAik: Okay, leave it for now. Let work, then I will tell you.
Krish NAik: So, actually, when you have executed that command, in that command, at the end also, you can add that hyphen hyphen instance profile.
Krish NAik: So that parameter can be added. Okay, let me update, paste it in Notion, it becomes easiest for one.
Krish NAik: Okay, so…
Krish NAik: Just wait, Gaza, I'm pasting one more command in Notion.
Krish NAik: You guys can actually take it from there.
Krish NAik: Okay, so I've, shared it in Notion. Okay, and let me just,
Krish NAik: share you this. Okay, now, have you got any error? Please, reload the file.
Krish NAik: It will take some time to do that.
milind kulkarni: Not yet HDM.
Krish NAik: Okay, we're waiting for answers. Till now, no error means fine. No error means fine, everybody.
milind kulkarni: No, earlier I'll say it was going up too, but I think this time the rejected an added instance to your environment.
milind kulkarni: And if I go to old one…
milind kulkarni: We're saying that, okay, remove extension.
milind kulkarni: Create.
milind kulkarni: instance. Added instance. After that, it was failing.
Krish NAik: Look, and let's see.
Rajat Khanna: Paul, Dan, can you see my screen?
Krish NAik: Yes, I can see your screen title.
Rajat Khanna: Okay, so I have updated it here.
Krish NAik: is…
Rajat Khanna: In that you told, and…
Krish NAik: After doing this, you have to do an EV create.
Krish NAik: As simple as that. You can do an EV create.
Rajat Khanna: So, I have done termination of the previous one, because.
Krish NAik: Yes, if you have terminated it directly, you can run the command db create, that's the only thing.
Krish NAik: Because after that, the same thing that needs to be attached.
Krish NAik: Because I think you guys already have the policies.
Rajat Khanna: Okay…
Krish NAik: Attached to that.
Rajat Khanna: Okay.
Krish NAik: I'm adding that entire thing.
Krish NAik: Okay, here you can actually pass that parameter also, hyphen hyphen instance profiler that I have added in Notion.
Krish NAik: Shall we stop the previous process? Yes, you can stop and terminate, if you have actually not done that, because for most of you, it should work, but again, a few verification stuff.
Krish NAik: With respect to policies and, attached things, just wait.
Krish NAik: I will add one more.
Rajat Khanna: In stance, it is coming as unrecognized argument.
Krish NAik: leave that part then, I think manually I've added hyphen hyphen profile, I think that command, I will check the invoice. I have not executed that, but that was the other way around.
Krish NAik: Just a minute.
Krish NAik: So, where is… in Notion, I've added one command, just to check that whether you have the permission or not, okay?
Krish NAik: Because with your policy, if there is some problem directly, like, then you will get that particular error.
Rajat Khanna: So for me, if I go…
Krish NAik: Okay, so, like.
Rajat Khanna: Just wait, you can stop sharing.
Krish NAik: Let me share my screen and let me show others exactly what I'm doing.
Krish NAik: Okay, so right here, as you can see, okay, so in my case, it was successful. I've added this AWS IAM attached rule policies, and then this is the AWS Elastic Beanstalk EC2 rule. Okay, so in your case, the rule name is exactly the same one that you have used, and please check the policies here.
Krish NAik: This policy, Amazon EC2 Container Registry Read Only, it should be available.
Krish NAik: If it is not available, guys, it can create a problem. Okay? So this is the command, the same command I have pasted it in, where? In Notion, yes. In Notion, you can directly get the last command. Okay, so here I will add as a command policy check command.
Krish NAik: Okay, our policy, check.
Krish NAik: command.
Krish NAik: Hmm.
Krish NAik: Now, once you have done till this point, then directly, like, okay, once after checking the policy, you can run the same command.
Krish NAik: Like, create.
Krish NAik: E and V, okay, and let me paste the command here.
Krish NAik: Okay, then comes your normal, the same thing that you can do. For now, I will test this one. As you were telling, it is not working.
Krish NAik: Okay, so… Let me just delete this one. Once I test it, then we'll add it.
Krish NAik: Because for me, without this one directly worked, but, please have it checked, because this is the main line that needs to be added. Okay, and if you have added this line number, I think 12,
Krish NAik: Fine, check the policy. If the policy is available, okay, you can get the verification from your terminal, like this Amazon container EC2 read only. If this is available, then please try directly doing an EB create.
Krish NAik: Okay? So, step by step. First of all, just if…
Krish NAik: I can say terminate the old one, update the config.yml file, line number 12, add the name of the policy and the name of the role, actually, not the policy, it's actually the role.
Krish NAik: In the instance profile field, okay, and let me just show you here, I think here, line number.
milind kulkarni: I think it's still failed for me. I have the roll, I checked it.
milind kulkarni: Hmm.
Krish NAik: Okay, just check, then again I will, come to you.
milind kulkarni: Yeah, noticed.
Krish NAik: What is the error that you are getting? Docker.
milind kulkarni: Same, Dr. Amish Field.
Krish NAik: really, like, if I feel that if you have this…
Krish NAik: EC2 container. Others, also, please provide a confirmation.
milind kulkarni: the low…
milind kulkarni: Yeah, I checked the role, and I… there is a four role to that, there are four…
milind kulkarni: for.
Krish NAik: See, these are.
milind kulkarni: Permissions.
milind kulkarni: Hour, yeah, I see there are horse.
milind kulkarni: No, go to… like, if I go to roles, right, and then EC2 Roles…
Krish NAik: Even I'm going through the rules.
milind kulkarni: Yeah.
milind kulkarni: AWS Elastic Beanstalk.
Krish NAik: Yes.
milind kulkarni: And then there are 4 holes there, right?
Rajat Khanna: Paul, still that authentication report error is there.
Krish NAik: Okay.
milind kulkarni: Hello.
Krish NAik: There are… let me see if we have a point.
Rajat Khanna: Okay.
Krish NAik: Authentication is still feeling, because for that specific profile, Just quit.
Krish NAik: Now, see, I will terminate my entire thing, okay, because that is the other way around that I can think about, just with…
Krish NAik: I will delete everything for my entire me net.
Krish NAik: Okay, and then, hyphen, hyphen, all let me add that.
Krish NAik: hyphen, hyphen…
Krish NAik: I'm deleting everything, from my site, so just wait.
Krish NAik: Alrighty, in the meantime, I will stop sharing. My deletion will take 5 minutes, so I can look into somebody else's screen. Yes, there, show me anyone.
Krish NAik: Alright, because there is no specific command, it's there, the entry is there in pyproject.2ml.
Krish NAik: So, there is no command for that, for CPU build creation. Yes.
Rajat Khanna: So, I have done, the Luminate again, just to, reiterate, like, the instance profile is…
Krish NAik: If you have stopped, then date, you have to do the termination of that particular environment, then recreate.
milind kulkarni: Paul, can I share my screen? I can see the error. I downloaded that EV engine log.
milind kulkarni: Let me…
Krish NAik: It will be in your local machine also.
Krish NAik: Yes. I think you can, share.
Krish NAik: Where is, please raise your hand.
Krish NAik: Milind, melinder? Melinda.
Krish NAik: I think, Milint, okay, we were back to Adria.
Krish NAik: So, just… I've added you, please start sharing.
Krish NAik: Because this, because I know this will be some type of
Krish NAik: Instance profile none, this is a problem.
Krish NAik: Yes, tell me now, what is the log that you are telling me? EV engine log, yes?
Krish NAik: It's telling no space lepton device.
Krish NAik: No space left on Deva Ace.
Krish NAik: space… I am taking a bigger one.
Krish NAik: Scroll down below.
Krish NAik: Okay, engine with respect to ground lock, CV, auto-scaling.
Krish NAik: Alright, because in my case, I have not, used auto-scaling and other things.
Krish NAik: Okay, fine, scroll down below. Any other thing is there? Because, this is the bundle locks, fine. Then I think other than that. And now, just show me the main error from your, that one.
Krish NAik: No, no, no, no, not this one. Your main one. Docker, that, I think, failing one.
Krish NAik: Because… because it's telling a disk issue.
Krish NAik: I… I am using pretty big one, T3.large, higher RAM, higher DEXIS, so…
Krish NAik: The disk management issue… let me…
Krish NAik: Because… That is fine.
Krish NAik: Mmm, let's see once.
Krish NAik: Okay, fine. Because, the instance profiler command… for me, I, again, I will do it from scratch, let's see what happens.
Krish NAik: Alright.
Krish NAik: Because the problem that you are getting, no, so now, because the other way around is, like, I manually increase the size of elastic bean also.
Krish NAik: the default one, I will make it 30GB.
Krish NAik: That is the other way around, but let's see step by step.
Krish NAik: Alright guys, so now, according to the error that you are getting, okay, so don't create, don't create, don't create, don't create, do a Ctrl-Z. Just wait. First of all, let me provide…
Krish NAik: storage, extension, okay? Just wait.
Krish NAik: So just wait, I will share my screen, everybody. As you can see, I've done the termination.
Krish NAik: Okay, because I thought within 8GB, it should work, that's why. But, let's see. I have deleted entirely, I don't have anything right now. Okay, so if I go here, if I show you my environment variables, okay? So everything is terminated right now. Okay, so pretty much clean stuff, nothing here.
Krish NAik: Now, we're redoing it from scratch, okay? Now, according to the size issue, first of all, that you are facing, okay? So, let's go here.
Krish NAik: Okay, I have, I think, this one that I have created.
Krish NAik: No work tree is all right, fine.
Krish NAik: Okay, I am adding this, increase ABS storage.
Krish NAik: I'm adding one file. Please use this file.
Krish NAik: Increase EVF storage. I am adding a 30GB storage right now. Okay, for safety limits, it's…
Krish NAik: Because of some reason, if it got increased.
Krish NAik: storage.config. Now, this is the file which needs to be available under .ev extensions, okay? So, increasing the EVS storage from 8GB to 30GB.
Krish NAik: Let's…
Krish NAik: I think,
Krish NAik: Okay, so everybody, please check, this, branch. Okay, I have added one file just to handle the…
Krish NAik: Extensions for now, and very specifically, the size of the…
Krish NAik: Size of what, the,
Krish NAik: EVS storage that I have increased from 8 to 30.
Krish NAik: Yep, so just wait, let me go to my…
Krish NAik: There, let me just reload this.
Krish NAik: Can you see this .ev extension's a new folder? Okay, and here I've kept the storage.config.
Krish NAik: Okay, so here you can see 30, root volume size that I have kept it. Previously, it was 8, but looks like it was… was not working, so manually now I will increase the size.
Krish NAik: According to the error, like, millions was getting, so I feel that a few people might get it, so let's…
Krish NAik: increase the size in one shot, and with respect to T3 large, I have 8GB of RAM, so I'll feel the execution.
Krish NAik: should work. Because for me, last time also the deployment worked, but again, let's try to do the deployment from scratch.
Krish NAik: Alright, now I will go back to my, terminal?
Krish NAik: Okay? So, let's… So, first of all, what I need, if you remember, what are the things? First, I need to create an EVCreate, okay?
Krish NAik: This is the instance type that I'm passing, okay, and the same thing that I'm doing. EB, create, okay, CRAG, ragproud, okay? There is nothing changed. I have just added that .ebextensions folder, and inside that, I have my storage configuration.
Krish NAik: Other than that, rest, everything is same. Okay, are you sharing? I think my… I'm sharing the screen. Which screen are you seeing?
Krish NAik: Because I think this is the desktop 2 only I'm sharing.
Krish NAik: Please let me know. Can you see my screen? Because, again, I'm restarting the entire deployment, guys. Please let me know.
Krish NAik: Okay? Alright, see. Now, what is the main change that I have done? If you go here, okay, so here…
Krish NAik: Here, there's .tv extensions, and then you have your storage.config.
Krish NAik: Okay, now here I've just added this file.
Krish NAik: That's the only thing. Rest, everything is fine. So now what I will do… yeah, so here, first of all,
Krish NAik: Let me create that one. Okay, C rag, okay, and prod, okay, alright, hyphen hyphen single, very important. Now, let me park, then let me see…
Krish NAik: Okay, alright, AB init, I didn't get it, let me do that AB init also.
Krish NAik: I thought I didn't win.
Krish NAik: Okay, yes, I think this is the first one.
Krish NAik: My spelling mistake right now.
Krish NAik: Alright.
Krish NAik: Alright, once this is done, then I think I can go ahead with the creation, EV create, CRAG.
Krish NAik: app, okay? So, EV in it done, then in the next step, I am executing the creation of the main environment, where my EC2, ECR, all those things that will be launched.
Krish NAik: Okay, so let's see.
Krish NAik: This will take time, so let's wait 3-4 minutes.
Rajat Khanna: Paul, I have a question here. You have done EB init CRAG app, and in the init it is app, and in create, it is prod. Does that make any difference?
Krish NAik: No, no, that is the main one. Inside that, you can have multiple environments, there is no issue in that.
Rajat Khanna: Okay, and in the prod, so, as I told you previously, in the, that,
Rajat Khanna: that project, that file that is there, no? You told the, the same name, the same name should be there.
Krish NAik: Generally, it's a good practice, otherwise you can keep multiple environments.
Krish NAik: Inside and involved. There is no issue in that.
Rajat Khanna: So, if I do…
Krish NAik: You can run multiple applications within a single environment, that is the idea in Elastic Beanstalk.
Rajat Khanna: Okay, if I do EB createCRAG app, it will… it will make no, issue.
Krish NAik: another environment.
Krish NAik: you just keep on changing EV create track name, more and more environment will be created. More and more application environment.
Rajat Khanna: If I'm doing just EB createCRAG app, it will not make any authentication error, because currently I'm just saying authentication error again and again.
Krish NAik: But you have to, alright, fine, then by default, check what will be the instance type that will be getting allocated. And if you don't pass iPhone FN single, by default, it will switch on auto-scaling and load balancing, which are the things not required. So, I have passed those parameters.
Rajat Khanna: Let's see, I'll… I'll do EB Create again.
Krish NAik: It was once the EC2 was launched.
Krish NAik: Then in the next step, because I think for most of you, this step you are failing. Yes or no? Please let me know in the chat.
Krish NAik: Because once this step is done, you need to set the environment with variables and update the environment, okay? So, let's wait, because right now I have told you everything.
Krish NAik: Now, let's increase the storage data also I have done. Okay, after increasing the storage, I have added the instance profile also in config.yml, so I don't feel there are any other things…
Krish NAik: Very specifically. Okay, so just wait.
Krish NAik: Well, this process takes time.
Abhishek: So, Paul, for me, I think it's already, I mean, stuck at creating application version archive only.
Krish NAik: Till now, he was talking to Deadline only.
Abhishek: this…
Krish NAik: Stop that. Stop that, and then, like,
Krish NAik: Use the command to delete everything, your environment and everything. Okay, so for that, you can use, like, EV space terminate, hyphen hyphen all hyphen hyphen force.
Krish NAik: Okay, and then try to recreate, do an EV in it, and then try to do it again.
Abhishek: Okay.
Krish NAik: But use that parameter, hyphen hyphen all and hyphen hyphen force.
Abhishek: Okay, sure, sure.
Krish NAik: Biology study how to reduce the Docker image size, please let me know. Like, my image size is 1.5 and all, like, what is your size biology?
Krish NAik: Because the code is exactly the same, that 4.5GB means that you need to debug that issue. That while Dockling is picking up the GPU builder PyTorch.
Krish NAik: Okay, that is them, because, see, I've been using the same script for most of them, it's 1.5. But for a few people, I think, like, Poonam also mentioned, okay, you also… okay, like, 4 or 5 people are telling you it's not working.
Krish NAik: Okay, so that's why I feel that there can be a workaround is there, I know, like, through requirement.txt a little bit.
Krish NAik: architectural changes that I have to do.
Krish NAik: But, yes, it is possible. Okay? So, see, right now, it worked for me. So, again, you guys can let me know that it worked.
Krish NAik: If it worked, then only I have to move to the next step of setting up the environment variables. So, everybody, please let me.
Krish NAik: Okay, so please… do this. In the meantime, I will update my ENV, variable also.
Krish NAik: Okay, now these are my environment variables.
Krish NAik: Okay, my OpenAI API key tabula quadrant.
Krish NAik: It takes some time to update the environment once the environment variables are updated. Then, in the next step, I will be passing
Krish NAik: to update the application through EV space, deploy.
Krish NAik: Okay, let's see.
Krish NAik: Imran is sharing, sir, in local, I checked, the image size, it's around 4.5GB, but in ECR, it's, is that fine? Yes, later on, it gets compressed.
Krish NAik: When you actually upload it, so few things actually get compressed.
Krish NAik: Initi.
Krish NAik: Please look into the final ECR, don't look into your local MRA.
Krish NAik: Always look into that, because everybody applies some level of compression.
milind kulkarni: I'm trying to rebuild it now.
Krish NAik: Obviously, after that, you can add, hyphen hyphen all.
Krish NAik: Abhishek, okay? Like, hyphen, hyphen all, and after that, hyphen, hyphen forth, and that will delete everything, try to do that. Yes.
Krish NAik: What are you telling? Tell?
milind kulkarni: I copied that storage extension one.
milind kulkarni: And now, trying to recreate it.
milind kulkarni: You recreate the build stock environment.
Krish NAik: Which environment? Please let me know.
milind kulkarni: No, no, I copied that storage file, right? That EB extension. You said that…
Krish NAik: Yes, it is already pushed into the branch. You can do.
milind kulkarni: Yay!
Krish NAik: automatically. Yes. Yes, once you have done this, then you can actually recreate and restart your deployment. The size review is resolved now.
Krish NAik: I don't think we'll be having any size issue right now.
Krish NAik: Alright, it's telling the environment updated successfully. Alright, fine. Now let's look into the URL. Where is the URL, I think?
Krish NAik: This is the URL, yes.
Krish NAik: Let's see, okay, can you see? Yes, it's broken, I can see here. Okay, so at least, till this point, everybody, say, again, I did the redeployment, everything in front of you, please let me know. Because in my case, if I show you really, like, my GitHub.
Krish NAik: If I register… Because this elastic reinstall config.
Krish NAik: Okay, and if you, really look into instance profile, I have not added that.
Krish NAik: Because for me, like, knowledge working.
Krish NAik: So, because of that, I feel that, okay, and please do check this config.yml.
Krish NAik: Okay, because here, CRAG app brought, then CRAG app, again, this one, in my case, environment and the application level are different, but I think it should be up and running, and this is my main initialization. So please do have a check on this one, because
Krish NAik: For me, it's working, at least…
Krish NAik: Five of you tell me that, yes, it's working.
Krish NAik: It will take time, but again, please do have a check and then, provide me the final update.
Krish NAik: Because if you see, the step is pretty much a repetitive one, so I don't think that 30GB right now will create any type of disk issue or anything like that.
Krish NAik: And, right now, if I look into the logs…
Krish NAik: You can look for the logs from here also. Now see, these are all application logs that I have.
Krish NAik: Okay, so, alright, evening one.
Krish NAik: Starting off, loading container start, docker demand, daemon has started, API is listening slash run slash docs.
Krish NAik: OpenTelemetry, container ID, through that. Okay, majorly, like, I cannot see any type of error level, but have a check.
Krish NAik: I've created too many environments, so cleaning it up, okay, alright. Just delete, that's why, like, EV space…
Krish NAik: Terminate, space, again, hyphen, hyphen, fourth, hyphen, hyphen all, just delete everything.
Krish NAik: It's better.
Krish NAik: Because too many things can create a problem. So, it's better just to be sure you are starting from scratch, the same way that I have done.
Krish NAik: Pratamesh, the same question. Pratamehai. T, Pratamesh.
Krish NAik: You are asking the question, should I purchase the newly… in that, first of all, check the syllabus. The things check what you are.
Krish NAik: Because, like,
Krish NAik: My syllabus, I think, next month in March, first week. I'm planning to add reinforcement learning also, and a few other things.
Krish NAik: But, check, because I feel that the upgraded one, I'll be adding similar content, but again, if you feel there are certain basic things that I won't be including in that course.
Krish NAik: Okay, so, Pratmej, I feel that only because of 2 to 3 modules, which might be not known to you.
Krish NAik: Okay, so, just wait, you have time.
Krish NAik: wait till March.
Krish NAik: 13th or 14th?
Krish NAik: the first class after the induction, Pratamesh, okay, I will share the draft version of the advanced one.
Krish NAik: Okay? That 50-60% that I have planned. Rest…
Krish NAik: You can take your decision, Prathamish.
Krish NAik: Eddie?
Krish NAik: Moving.
Krish NAik: If you feel more than 30-40% things are totally unknown to you, then it's a good practice to purchase.
Krish NAik: We're taking.
Krish NAik: the advanced one, I was planning, because for… in the RAG, how to use reinforcement learning, everywhere, like, many people are not comfortable with reinforcement learning, fine-tuning, those type of things only. The things which make people uncomfortable, those topics, I will keep it much more.
Krish NAik: No, no, it will be after your complete ride, like, I will be taking…
Krish NAik: It will be a continuous discussion, because that will be US timing, basically, not Indian timing. Morning, I am planning, morning or evening. Any US people, you can let me know, like, what's a good time? Like, Indian 5 o'clock, or evening 5 o'clock, because evening 5 or 5.30, if I go, it will be morning for you guys.
Krish NAik: Because, those two slots are there morning.
Krish NAik: You know, like, morning it becomes…
Krish NAik: problem a little bit, because again, from 9 o'clock, I'll be having one class.
Krish NAik: So that's why, that input I want to take only from US students and others. Indian students, not an issue.
Krish NAik: But, Eva's guys can let me know that.
Krish NAik: Within it.
Krish NAik: Because in India, timing, I will be having, like, continuous sessions, that's the only thing.
Krish NAik: Indian timing, 8 is not possible, Mohammutza, because from 9 o'clock in from the month of August, I'll be having another batch.
Krish NAik: If I start the batch from June or July, like, it will be a conflict. That is the main problem. The slot is only not available.
Krish NAik: All right.
milind kulkarni: So, for the US, it might be 6.30 or something will work perfect.
milind kulkarni: I mean, West Coast?
Krish NAik: Yes.
milind kulkarni: Still have a problem, right? But the east and central will be okay.
Krish NAik: That's a dead timing, I can actually increase, so…
Krish NAik: My main problem is, like, from the month of August, I'll be getting UDS 2.0, there I have to teach deep learning, okay? Now, that thing is, like, morning 9, which batch got launched last month. That will come to me in the month of… probably, let's take August or September. If I start the batch, I know, like.
Krish NAik: 2-3 months is fine, but after that, then that, will happen. Okay, so clash will happen with respect to the West. So it's better, like, I can do it in the morning or in the evening. Both the slots are fine.
Krish NAik: That's why that decision… people who are interested, I'll be keeping a one-to-one discussion on that, okay? Now, people just focus on the deployment and let me know that, yes, it is working or not. It's better tomorrow?
milind kulkarni: Pardon me.
milind kulkarni: But I… I had to change the… the config.yaml in the binstock to environment name.
milind kulkarni: Like, create an environment with a different name.
milind kulkarni: But.
Krish NAik: Then manually you have updated the config.yml.
milind kulkarni: Yes.
milind kulkarni: And then it did an environment of… I did that EV setup environment also.
milind kulkarni: And that's also true.
Krish NAik: Alright, now, like, application is up and working, let me know that, but…
milind kulkarni: I'm taking that one.
milind kulkarni: But to do that, I need to update the environment variable first, right?
Krish NAik: We are pretty much done with the class right now.
Krish NAik: And just, okay.
Krish NAik: Yes, because if the application is working, Mantaj, in your case, is it working? Have you tested it? Then you are good to go. Then tomorrow, I will add that CI pipeline and other things. Satish, yes, yes, yes.
Prathmesh Atre: Hi, sir.
Krish NAik: You can ESS still.
Prathmesh Atre: Actually, I'm pretty confused, so asking again, like, as I said, I enrolled in.
Krish NAik: Now, see, what is your requirement? See, whenever you purchase… I purchase Coors…
Krish NAik: Majorly, when I feel that, there is 10% to 15% at least, differences there.
Krish NAik: Okay.
Prathmesh Atre: Actually, I have seen a few topics, like, of the AWS, like, there are a few services that you're telling about, like, recognition and all, so that part is.
Krish NAik: Don't worry, see, see, in this part only, once you are completed with Project 3, I told I will create a dedicated team, like, right now.
Krish NAik: If you saw, like, Rahul shared that he was working in that part. Similarly, like, I will create a team of 5 to 6 people in a group, parallel, like, if you want to create the entire stack in AWS, okay, then for them, then all those things with respect to, for example, with respect to your multimodal support, then everything from
Krish NAik: All those AWS services will be completed. Don't think about that. It's just a rack-specific, like, people who are good in Azure, you can let me know, 5 to 6 people. I will create a group, and you guys create only it in Azure, one only in GCP. So that those three stacks, according to cloud-specific things, and later on.
Krish NAik: We guys can, like, interconnect, and we can give a demo, and things, we can make it clear.
Krish NAik: Okay, once we do the project 3, then we can do that.
Krish NAik: Okay, so don't worry about that AWS services. Okay, Pratunaj.
Prathmesh Atre: All right, all right, sir. And what you were saying about the further advanced batch that you are launching, like, it is not the one who's already launched for the March, right? It is the.
Krish NAik: It's not the one. My batch will come after Agent, because after Sunny's batch, Mank will launch Agent Sino. After Agent's batch, then, like,
Krish NAik: Because I'll be taking one month vacation, because I have two classes, so my… after my vacation, it will be May last week, or June 1st week.
Krish NAik: So, enough time is there, like, I will be having weekly meetings, at least, because the batch will be completed, but from your batch, very specifically, like, I'll be taking a few meetings just to discuss on the syllabus.
Prathmesh Atre: So it will be, again, the kind of third one that you're going to launch, like, the one that is already being there, then the main of agents, and then yours will be there.
Krish NAik: Yes, yes, yes. Because it won't be a rag batch. A rag batch will be a different batch. That will be a little bit towards advanced LLMs.
Krish NAik: Like, SLM fine-tuning in Sunny's Batch, I think it's there, but, in my case, it will be much more, SLMs I'll be using, which are much more, like, industry-based. Like, if you guys know about Liquid AI, Liquid AI has very good LLMs. SLMs, sorry, not LLMs.
Prathmesh Atre: Absolutely.
Krish NAik: that part.
Krish NAik: A few things I'll be taking, and even with respect to reinforcement learning, that part. Like, in RAG, how you can…
Krish NAik: Build a reward-bid system.
Krish NAik: A lot of other optimizations that in this course we have not discussed. Like, I know that in this course I can discuss more and more things, but a few things from there, so certain discussions that I'll be taking from this batch, and I'll be including in that batch.
Prathmesh Atre: Alright, so this… that would be the kind of advancement of this one.
Krish NAik: That will be much advanced. It will be pure R&D stuff.
Prathmesh Atre: I'm…
Krish NAik: There, my objective is not to productionize things, we have to understand. For productionized things, from this batch, most of you know the services, so you can actually take it up. They're integrating multiple things into a single environment.
Krish NAik: much more little bit towards microservices, because in Project 3 also, little bit microservices that we will discuss, but again, not from the entire
Krish NAik: certain things with respect to security and other things also that I am planning.
Prathmesh Atre: Thank you.
Prathmesh Atre: It's actually also the one concern is, like, let's say when we are doing things, how to securely, do, you know, and when we are having, let's say, the kind of MCP tool that we are exposing, then how to provide the, you know, rule-based access, or who can access them, so these kind of security-based things.
Krish NAik: RBAC system, see, MCP servers, generally, I don't… I have never used it in production, I don't know how many people are using it, but I have never used it in production. Rather than, for example, vector databases and other things, I can create something like an RBAC system, completely rule-based.
Krish NAik: Like, if somebody is hitting… because that's a very important thing in an organization, who is accessing which information.
Prathmesh Atre: Right, right.
Krish NAik: Whenever they are actually accessing RAC, this is very, very important.
Krish NAik: Later on, because some confidential information should not be available to someone. So that part, guardrails, prompt injection, yes, actually, there are certain other things also, that's called as data poisoning.
Krish NAik: Okay, few… those are much more security-level topics that I'll be including in the next one. But I'll be… I have kept a note, but I'm thinking about, in reinforcement learning, exactly what to add.
Krish NAik: It'll be much more R&D-based stuff.
Krish NAik: Rather than building apps.
Prathmesh Atre: that you said is related to agents. Is it like the agentic bar that you launched, like Agentic V1, V2, is it kind of.
Krish NAik: Agents will be like agents 2.0 or 1.0, like 4 or 5 frameworks with respect to agents, and I think in A10 and other things that Mank is much more better. I only be dealing with agents, because in agents, there is nothing to do with respect to R&D, that's why.
Prathmesh Atre: Because you already launched the two ones, right? Like, the V1 and V2.
Prathmesh Atre: Like, I already unlearn in the V1 version.
Krish NAik: I can say more than 70%, probably one or two frameworks might be added, because again, the AutoGen stuff has deprecated a lot of updates with respect to those frameworks and those things will become.
Prathmesh Atre: Hmm, right.
Krish NAik: Time is there, like…
Rajat Khanna: Edmund.
Krish NAik: just because my batch I am planning, it can be June, July also. Because once I discuss, then actually, I'll be taking a team, and a few other things that I have kept. It will be an advanced batch, so I know the number of enrollments will be low, but I'll be focusing on R&D stuff much more. That's all.
Prathmesh Atre: And also, like, if, like, we are very focused natively on the AWS, so if it's possible, like, in one of the badge, you also focus on, you know, the Azure part heavily, so that…
Krish NAik: I'm not good in Azure, okay? Like, I don't use Azure. True to say. I only use AWS. If Azure comes into the picture, I bring some other guy into the picture. That's why, like, everybody is good in something. I have worked much more on GCP and AWS my entire life.
Krish NAik: Okay, later, because from day one, I didn't got exposure in my starting four years in Azure, so I never actually went ahead with Azure.
Krish NAik: My entire startup, and everything that I worked, it was in AWS and GCP. The initial, credits were in GCP, so I'm good in GCP and I'm good in that. So, and even for students, I feel that
Krish NAik: Azure is much more expensive. From enterprise point, it's much more used in India, then the market comes to AWS, so I feel that, yes, we can discuss, but I know in this patch, there will be at least 5 students, or 6 students, who knew that Azure stuff.
Krish NAik: So we'll be… we'll try to identify them, and in that way, because that's the idea for the RAG infra also, that an entire RAG using only the cloud services and not getting out of the system.
Prathmesh Atre: And, yeah. And, that's.
Krish NAik: We just need to identify the students, okay, so probably, just wait, like, once I will be back in Bangalore around the first week after Huli, then we'll be looking into, like, whoever is trying to pass their inputs, and then we can start working in that. As a separate project, it might take one minute, one month, or two months.
Krish NAik: But the idea is to do the completion, having a weekly meeting, separate to Saturday and Sundays, one time, according to you guys who are working, you can let me know. Then we can discuss, and then we can discuss it in this particular batch, once the final project is done. And that way, we can plan stuff.
Prathmesh Atre: Also, like, you can add pretty much things about the software engineering, like authentication, authorization, and it's not about, like, purely the AI, but how can we add the software engineering into the AI? So that's also actually important, because 20-30%.
Krish NAik: So right now, let's keep it… see, in one shot, let's not… I… step by step. See, baby steps, let's take, because again, that thing, I need to see, like, 5 students, I know out of those 5, 2 will be active, 3 won't be. A lot of other things comes into the picture when actually you give tasks to someone.
Krish NAik: Because right now, there are AI. So, my idea is that you people will be highly utilizing AI for your work stuff.
Krish NAik: In AI, what happens? You need to actually sit and you need to do the execution and experiment much more, which AI can't do it. So, that part, let's do it. Wait for project 3 completion.
Prathmesh Atre: It's possible to do next ones, like, that you are planning. So, in that also, if that, things are getting covered, that is also fine.
Krish NAik: I will take that input, don't worry. Next batch planning, I will do it for 2 months, I have it in my mind.
Prathmesh Atre: Also, like, I suggested to Krishnak itself that they have also mailed to us and back, like, they will think of this, and, like, the voice-related things, if you can, you know… I also told it to you.
Krish NAik: Excuse me.
Prathmesh Atre: It's…
Krish NAik: voice-related stuff, building actual voice agents, if you're using Assembly AI 11Labs, it's pretty much it. But if you're not using them, and if you're actually personally using, like, Kokoro, Kik and TTS, like, manually who are hosting, then it becomes much more tougher.
Krish NAik: When you actually create that agent…
Prathmesh Atre: Only that managed services itself, like, we can directly use them, but even how to do that using them is, like, also the.
Krish NAik: I think. You can, like… Let's see.
Prathmesh Atre: See, we can do multiple things, but you have to think that the students need to…
Krish NAik: Like, I'm the guy, I cannot do everything, okay?
Prathmesh Atre: Good night.
Krish NAik: divide 55 people, or 66 people, those 66 people can start working in some unique project, those batches. So, in the next batch, I'll be taking much more cohort-based systems. Like, each cohort will be focused on a single task.
Krish NAik: And at least by the end of that, I think some good things can come out, if you guys at least have one month or two months to work on a certain thing. Yes or no? Because that's my plan. Rather than keeping it much more one-sided, I feel that the interaction between the peers should be much more, that's why.
Krish NAik: Because in the current system, it's not there, but again, for that batching, when I'm planning to use a dedicated Matterport server also that I was planning, to get it and use it only for those students.
Krish NAik: Because right now, the communication is a big barrier that I feel, somehow.
Krish NAik: Because the forum, even I don't love it.
Krish NAik: sometimes I open the page and I actually respond. So, just wait till March, because in the entire month of April, because your batch might be ending, but I'll be keeping weekly meetings, at least. Because what should be the next step that even you are planning in your head? Few things from you guys that I'll be taking some input.
Krish NAik: Based on… because 50-60% will be my decision, rest, polling and other things.
Krish NAik: We will take the decision. So just wait for, like, till batch, I think, till March 15th, then I will start the next fight.
Prathmesh Atre: At that time, you will, like, post the syllabus, right?
Krish NAik: initial wrapped it will be. Then, after that, at least 5 to 6 meetings that I'm planning to keep it, because few things you might feel that, okay, we have already learned in this course.
Krish NAik: Let's remove that module. So, it will be your decision, because the idea is not to make things repetitive for me also. Okay, so if it's removed, then what are the things that are not discussed in RAG only? So, that part… like, one module will be for LLM, then one module for SLM,
Krish NAik: Then one module for really, like, introducing your different type of fine-tunings, PPO, DPO, RHLF, all those fine-tuning stuff. But on fine-tuning, you have to understand, when I try to do, you guys, if you do it, you have to spend some money, and the expectation is that at least using unlock to a certain level, it will be free.
Krish NAik: But at least, you have to think that you need to spend $50 to $100.
Krish NAik: Just to explode that stuff.
Prathmesh Atre: Pretty expensive, you know.
Prathmesh Atre: It must still be a bit off.
Krish NAik: Otherwise, people don't want to do, you can look at, like, a movie, it's stuff I'm doing, but the idea is at least 3 students are doing it, then I will feel that, yes.
Krish NAik: That's why. Otherwise, you create a group.
Prathmesh Atre: Okay, you would, like, 4 or 5 people using a single account. So, let's see, that's why a lot of discussions are there, actually, when I try to go into next level, because it becomes very niche, I know very less people will be joining.
Krish NAik: But it's fine. It's an experiment that I am ready to take a chance.
Prathmesh Atre: Okay, okay, sir, that will be a good initiative, actually, from your side.
Krish NAik: Great.
Krish NAik: Satish, I think you have raised your hand.
Krish NAik: And Aruna also.
Rajat Khanna: upon…
Krish NAik: tell me how many of you can see the application screen, at least. Let me know in the chat. Because by this time, all of your debugging… can you see something like this? Your main FastAPI homepage? Working for me already, those are fine. Anybody else?
Rajat Khanna: I can…
Abhishek: I can see that one, but query and document upload fails.
Krish NAik: Okay, alright, that part is fine. That is application-level error that we can actually look into and we can resolve.
Rajat Khanna: I wonder if I am still into that, authentication one error, can I assure you I have terminated at it all the.
Krish NAik: Just wait, alright? You have documented.
milind kulkarni: Call tweak, right? We can… we can drop now, right?
Krish NAik: If you need help.
milind kulkarni: And terminate and recreate.
Krish NAik: Just do that EV, everybody, whoever has launched, just be sure you are using the command EV space terminate space.
Krish NAik: Like, hyphen, hyphen 4, space, hyphen, hyphen, all.
Krish NAik: This is a command, please, everybody execute, otherwise you will be charged very high, because monthly charges are close to $60 to $70.
Rajat Khanna: So one day you can think about make it divided by 60, so $2 easily that you will be getting charged.
Krish NAik: So, please, EV terminate hyphen FN4, hyphen hyphen all, verify it from the UI, and then only leave the session.
Krish NAik: Alright, Naga is telling I'm doing Azure LLM project to set meetings using calendar.
Krish NAik: Mmm… Alright, again, through calendars and other stuff, API stuff is there.
Abhishek: Paul, like, I am getting this file not found error. I'm not sure why…
Krish NAik: not found. Oh, show me that, show me that. Share your screen and show me.
Krish NAik: Because these things now, people have raised, and Satish, okay, I've asked you, Aruna also, I've asked you, okay, two things.
Abhishek: Can you see my street?
Krish NAik: Yes, I can.
Krish NAik: I can see, Vichick, your screen. It's telling the system cannot find .env.
Krish NAik: Then again, okay, one slash from here, then all backslashes came.
Krish NAik: D3 module…
Krish NAik: No, this is some application-level stuff, I feel. Just wait.
Abhishek: When I charge GPT, it is saying that it is some packaging error. File path is too long for Windows, archive phase. Okay.
Krish NAik: This happens actually only in Windows, I don't know. In, like, if it is folder within a folder, within, like, four levels of folder, it happens in Windows. I'm not sure exactly. You can keep this project probably in the, root directory of somewhere, like D drive or your E drive, and then you can try it out once.
Abhishek: Okay.
Krish NAik: Because this is a file not found error, and this is a Windows error, not related to AWS or any other thing.
Abhishek: Hmm, yeah, let me try that.
Krish NAik: Yes, Atish?
Satish Tiwari: Sir, I want to share my screen.
Krish NAik: Alright, Satisha, we'll add you.
Krish NAik: Aruna, you also can address. Others, please do have a check that the application part is working. Please. Okay, and then let me know that part.
Aruna: So I just need…
Krish NAik: Yes.
Krish NAik: Satisha, I think you can start sharing, you are in there.
Satish Tiwari: If I'm kidding.
Satish Tiwari: Is my sleep as well.
Krish NAik: Yes.
Satish Tiwari: Actually, I'm getting it out, While relieve these steps.
Krish NAik: Docker build, what is the error that you have… show me, show me. When you paste this particular command, you are on Windows, so remove that.
Satish Tiwari: Yes, Windows.
Krish NAik: So, show me. This is login succeeded done, then when you are building, remove that hyphen hyphen platform, first of all, when you are actually passing it.
Krish NAik: Docker build remove that hyphen platform Linux slash AMT64.
Satish Tiwari: Oh.
Satish Tiwari: Is it okay? iPhone, iPhone, I have removed.
Krish NAik: No, no, remove, remove entire platform, Linux slash Windows 64. By default, Windows motherboards, they support ARM64, okay?
Satish Tiwari: Minus.
Krish NAik: This is, okay, now, ECR repo, this variable, like, because, see, like, I don't know your ECR repo, so…
Satish Tiwari: Yes, this is ACA report.
Krish NAik: This is the ECR repo, right, okay, ECR repo. CRAC? No, this ECR repo has to be bigger, no, this is small, only CRAC.
Krish NAik: Just wait. Okay, you can hit an enter for this, you have to actually later do a tag. What I do, actually, I pass that entire ECR repo, thing. It's telling docker build X requires one argument.
Krish NAik: Just wait, let me see.
Krish NAik: I'm sharing one command in the chat, okay? Because according, I generally pass.
Krish NAik: This BuildX toolkit, manually, you can do it from the environment, you can switch it off, but before that, this… let me open my set.
Krish NAik: Where is the Z environment? Yes.
Krish NAik: You are asking for that particular command, docker build…
Krish NAik: Okay, so, like, I'm sharing mine one, you can, look into the chat one, Satish. Okay, so, like, in your case, remove. hyphen hyphen platform.
Krish NAik: Because I wouldn't think it would have actually required. Otherwise, keep it, but be sure that, that is hyphen T, that is the tag, and that is the entire ECR report that actually we were doing.
Krish NAik: Can you see that big thing?
Krish NAik: Before that.
Satish Tiwari: This one I have to remember now.
Krish NAik: If you… because it's not required, if you can keep it, it's a safety measure, that's why.
Satish Tiwari: And I have to change this account ID, correct?
Krish NAik: Check this, in front of me, execute, and then let me know.
Krish NAik: Because in Windows, for others also, it works, so I feel it should work for you also.
Satish Tiwari: Should I remove this one platform?
Krish NAik: Yeah, I think you already have the repo name, no? That you'll see a repo HDrag app latest.
Satish Tiwari: Like, they have…
Krish NAik: premium, no.
Satish Tiwari: I haven't updated that account ID.
Krish NAik: We'll be on retail.
Krish NAik: Like, if you get an error, just paste it in later.
Satish Tiwari: Yes.
Krish NAik: filter.
Satish Tiwari: Hilary's coming fairly.
Satish Tiwari: Okay.
Krish NAik: Because this is no such file or directory from where you are executing. Okay, there is no Docker file.
Krish NAik: So, where is the Docker file?
Satish Tiwari: Nope.
Satish Tiwari: See, I have checked that one, okay? In my Docker, that file is not there, but how to upload that thing is?
Krish NAik: No, no, I think it is in your other branch, no?
Satish Tiwari: I think you need it.
Satish Tiwari: Weird episode?
Krish NAik: Just right here, Git Space Branch.
Krish NAik: Because, you can do a git switch and the name of the branch, you can copy it from there.
Satish Tiwari: 3 inches. You want to see here, no?
Krish NAik: Because…
Satish Tiwari: So I have… no, no, actually, I am one of.
Krish NAik: In which branch you are? It doesn't look like you are in…
Satish Tiwari: Yes, yes, I was using that last week in UFC at that time.
Krish NAik: Okay, you can just paste here, write your git space branch first.
Satish Tiwari: No, this is my branch, okay? I'm using my… Beautiful.
Krish NAik: your branch, the right Git branch.
Krish NAik: No, do a git pull, please.
Krish NAik: Because today I shared another branch, no, with you. Okay, got it, got it. That Docker file should be there, here. That's why. You have not taken the latest pull. Please do the pull, and then it will work.
Satish Tiwari: Okay.
Satish Tiwari: Okay, got it.
Krish NAik: Okay. Alright, others, please let me know. Anybody?
Krish NAik: Aruna?
Aruna: Yeah, I had small requests, like, with two experience, if you can share some…
Aruna: examples to how to generate efficiently codes using different AI tools, and also some talk.
Krish NAik: I'll be taking that one session for Claude Code, as many people are the last class also. Yeah, yeah. Because at least for feature C, the idea is the things which Anthropic has officially told, those things I'll be discussing.
Krish NAik: Okay, I'll be keeping one session, because with respect to Cloud Code, and people who are using Claude Code, it's fine. Otherwise, follow the same rules for GLM or KimiCode also.
Krish NAik: Few things are different, but most of the things are good. Okay, so don't worry, I'll be taking a dedicated session. Just keep it as a separate session. I won't be taking this session right now, let's focus on a few major topics.
Krish NAik: then I can plan for that.
Rajat Khanna: Paul, can I show you now my.
Krish NAik: Yes, yes, you are in panelist only, you can start.
Rajat Khanna: Yeah, yeah, no, just wanted.
Rajat Khanna: So, still, I got the same error.
Krish NAik: What is the error?
Rajat Khanna: The authentication error.
Krish NAik: Authentication.
Rajat Khanna: authentication, private repository. So, now I have terminated all the instances. So, just to clarify.
Krish NAik: Before instance closing, you should have checked that, you know, logs, because…
Krish NAik: from the UI, you can actually download the logs, or, like, if you've already deleted it, then how I can check the logs? Because from the logs, you can actually get the idea that, why it is failing, the reason. For example, like, Millian told, then I know that, okay, the storage issue was there.
Krish NAik: That's why, like, exactly what is the main one.
Rajat Khanna: Now it's terminated, we cannot see the logs.
Krish NAik: Check once, because generally, after termination, most of the things are get deleted, that's why.
Rajat Khanna: Weird… Where I can find the logs.
Krish NAik: Even now, I'm not sure. Okay, where, click on that environment name in their…
Krish NAik: When you actually go to multiple application versions.
Rajat Khanna: No logs.
Krish NAik: Okay, go to, first of all, go to environment, because you are.
milind kulkarni: You should see, like, a request log, right? If you click on that.
Krish NAik: coffee.
milind kulkarni: Go there, go to logs.
Krish NAik: Click.
milind kulkarni: And then, yeah, logs.
Krish NAik: Blogs, not events.
milind kulkarni: And then, request log. Generally, when I did a request log, it will come for me.
milind kulkarni: So…
Krish NAik: In your case.
milind kulkarni: Nope.
Krish NAik: Looks like the application… Gordon… Tied, because of that, it's not showing.
milind kulkarni: Yeah.
Krish NAik: Click on that error. No, no, no, this is not your application-level log, these are EV-based logs.
milind kulkarni: That's how I got it. From there, I set a request log, and it downloaded.
Krish NAik: But right now, in your case, the logs are not being shown only.
Rajat Khanna: Okay, so, that, there is config file now, so in, in that you showed, to change the name, the permission name, something. So, now that.
Krish NAik: No, in storage.config, this is only for storage.
Rajat Khanna: No, no, there was another file, where, you told me the application name needs to be changed, instance name that needs to be changed, so that file is also get deleted.
Krish NAik: it was actually .ev, just with… I have not deleted that.
Rajat Khanna: No, no, you have not deleted, it's deleted. If we terminate the.
Krish NAik: Check the… I think one file will be there.elastic, beanstalk, dot… and that folder check. Inside that, you have that config.yman.
Krish NAik: There, you have the instance profile.
Rajat Khanna: I have only this, Elastic EB extensions, other… there is no folder now.
Krish NAik: Okay, I think, dot EVE extensions, dot beans… talk.
Krish NAik: Just retail portions.
Krish NAik: Alright, fine, because.
Rajat Khanna: What you can do, like, .elastic, dot beanstalk.
Krish NAik: This actually doesn't need to be, pushed, so I think…
Rajat Khanna: It is not available.beingstock is, that I have not pushed.
Krish NAik: Alright, so, like, this file gets automatically generated when you do an AB init.
Rajat Khanna: Okay.
Krish NAik: So, please do an EB in it right now, in front of me, whilst.
Krish NAik: Give any different thing.
Rajat Khanna: Okay.
Krish NAik: Because I feel that, it should be generated, for everyone it got generated, so for you also.
Krish NAik: Can you see? C. Dot.
Krish NAik: Okay, now inside this, you have your config. Now, here you have to update that line number 12, that EC2 profile, according to you, that needs to be added.
Krish NAik: You can check Notion from there, you will understand.
Krish NAik: Line number 12, that plus sign that I have added, that is the entry.
Krish NAik: Okay.
Krish NAik: Now, tomorrow, I will just add the CICD flow, okay, for this one, through a single shot that it gets deployed automatically.
Krish NAik: That will be the main flow, and with respect to the routes, I will have a check, because today we haven't checked the routes, so don't worry, tomorrow we will check the routes.
Krish NAik: For data.
Rajat Khanna: Okay, now, I will do that, creation.
Krish NAik: Mmm, yes.
Rajat Khanna: EB created C, correct?
Krish NAik: Yes, if you have majorly everything, start doing that. Then you will actually get… this will take some time.
Krish NAik: Alright, others, okay, somebody has addressed, Deva Jyoti Mukharchi, yes, Deva Jyoti.
DEBAJYOTI MUKHOPADHYAY: Yeah, so just one quick question, not related to today's work. You told that Microsoft Autogen is going to be obsolete, or maybe it is not…
Krish NAik: The name has changed, it's much more Microsoft Agentic. The name has changed, so some modules and everything will be
Krish NAik: The core functionality will remain same.
DEBAJYOTI MUKHOPADHYAY: Okay, because I have been part of the new, industry-grade project, the recent launch by Chris, right? So there, the first project was with AutoGen, and I'm learning AutoGen now, so I thought, am I doing something old stuff? That's not the case, right?
Krish NAik: No, no, no, see, the module is getting updated. It's not like that, see, the functionalities are there, but later on, when you actually switch to a different, project name, few modules, few inputs, the versioning, those things will change, but the core functionality will always remain the same.
DEBAJYOTI MUKHOPADHYAY: Okay, okay.
DEBAJYOTI MUKHOPADHYAY: Okay, I just have one more question. It is also out of the context for me. So, in my current project, actually, there is a… there is a kind of, there is a kind of architecture getting built where Microsoft Copilot's features are going to be explored.
DEBAJYOTI MUKHOPADHYAY: And, it is mainly, backside, we have the Power BI. In between, they are thinking of bringing the Copilot for the interactive chats over the dashboards and all, right? So, in that case, actually, any kind of RAG system could have taken any place, take any role, or Microsoft Copilot has everything inbuilt, we just have to do the plugin.
DEBAJYOTI MUKHOPADHYAY: play here. Any idea on it?
Krish NAik: No, no, see, Rag, the first question will come, like, why Rag?
Krish NAik: Do you have some type of external knowledge base that needs to be added?
DEBAJYOTI MUKHOPADHYAY: Definitely, that is it, right? Else, how could the co-pilot also retrieve? Yeah, that is probably needed.
DEBAJYOTI MUKHOPADHYAY: But I'm also not sure, but Microsoft Copilot has any kind of feature that it does the embeddings and all about.
Krish NAik: Because, by default, Microsoft Copilot can launch agents through which they can access files and other things.
Krish NAik: Okay, but again, like, now the question comes, if you have, like, 10,000 files, then it becomes a problem, just for a local agent to actually fetch it and access it.
Krish NAik: Then, when actually RAT can come into the picture. But if you have lesser number of files, for example, now these recent systems, whichever, like, if you look into CloudCo work and other things that are coming, to a limited its file, but actually, if you have many, many files, then again, that approach doesn't work out.
DEBAJYOTI MUKHOPADHYAY: I mean, data is quite huge, because we are, binding more than 7,000 plus reports under one dashboard, actually.
DEBAJYOTI MUKHOPADHYAY: And making it.
Krish NAik: In that case, what is the hierarchy of the system, how the, like, classification and the diversification of those files will be done?
Krish NAik: Need an idea, because, see, I don't feel everywhere rag needs to be attached.
Krish NAik: Till the time, if it's a valid requirement, then only I will be adding it.
DEBAJYOTI MUKHOPADHYAY: Okay, that's definitely… but I don't have that much of clarity, it's just initiated. But only question is, if in between, we would like to place some rag-based system between the co-pilot and the dashboard data, that is very much possible to do.
Krish NAik: Between the co-pilot, alright, co-pilot, again, agents will come, so yes, rack-based agents, automatically, co-pilot can take care of that. That is first thing. And then you were telling from,
Krish NAik: your, GitHub co-pilot to BI.
DEBAJYOTI MUKHOPADHYAY: Power BI, that we have.
Krish NAik: In between that, you want to bring the rag… picture.
DEBAJYOTI MUKHOPADHYAY: track-based agentic system, if you would like to build.
Krish NAik: See, GitHub Copilot is agents, so nothing is required. GitHub Copilot can take care of everything.
Krish NAik: Okay. I don't fail. If you need, see, what I will do, if you need a rag, I don't… I won't be bringing a rack, rather than I will be creating a tool. That will be a rag tool. Now, that rack tool, I will be attaching it to a, like, a co-pilot agent. I hope you get my point.
Krish NAik: I'll be using a customized tool, and I'll be invoking that whenever I require anything. So GitHub Copilot can do the entire stuff.
DEBAJYOTI MUKHOPADHYAY: Okay, and the customized tool will, do what, actually? It will be,
Krish NAik: For example, your rag will be invoking to some type of vector DB or some type of… now, that particular call, that tool will be invoked.
DEBAJYOTI MUKHOPADHYAY: Okay, for the retrieval.
Krish NAik: A simple rag tool you can think about, usually all the frameworks has that. If you don't need REST, that agent will decide when to invoke. Now, that will be your conditional logic, that based on this and this and this, you need to invoke that. Now, before invoking a certain
Krish NAik: I think you can, do much more filtering, because based on, like, 10,000 data, so how you can filter out your search.
DEBAJYOTI MUKHOPADHYAY: That optimization first do it, then invoke the tool, it's better always.
DEBAJYOTI MUKHOPADHYAY: Okay, okay.
Rajat Khanna: Paul, the… sharing my screen, so the same issue is there.
Krish NAik: Okay, now check into your logs. Go and check into your logs, because right now, let's see, Nitesh has raised… Nitesh, I have admitted you also.
Krish NAik: Go and now check the logs and request for logs. Yes, go.
Nitesh: Hey, Chris.
Krish NAik: books.
Nitesh: What do you hate Potter?
Krish NAik: tears.
Abhishek: While I'm still stuck at that same creating application, I put it…
Krish NAik: Okay, you are also getting that, main,
Krish NAik: Time out, now, what is the issue? Docker failed.
Krish NAik: Isshut, Ishu, Nitesh.
Nitesh: Hey, Paul, sorry. Hey, hey Paul, I think I just pasted into the chat as well, so actually…
Nitesh: I have missed the last one-month sessions, actually, due to some family emergency. So I was just, like, checking whether I should wait for a next project you are starting, maybe, tomorrow or next.
Krish NAik: Next… no, no, not next project. Before next project, I was planning to discuss…
Krish NAik: GraphRag then comes a little bit with respect to multimodal stuff. Haystack is remaining, no, one framework, so probably, one class or two class with respect to data and plus planning. Not to go a lot in details, but at least Haystack is mentioned, so…
Krish NAik: just wait one or two weeks, it will take time. Then, Project 4, next month, nothing in this month. Next month, I think after 10th or something like that, we'll be discussing Project 4. Because once Project 4 is done, then my entire focus will be towards agents, your land grab that you have in the syllabus.
Nitesh: Okay, so any suggestion on how I can catch it up, or maybe the project 3 which the team is trying to.
Krish NAik: image, like, if you… one month has been pretty hectic, really, to say. The Project 2 took a lot of time. I think Project 2A started from January 17th.
Nitesh: And, like, it took more than 6 sessions, so I think 10th of February.
Krish NAik: Till that time it took, so, majorly, if you have missed, I think it will be Project 2, and bits, because this Project 3 is much easier, actually, as compared to Project 2.
Krish NAik: So you can actually have a look into that, and after that, I took one session for, I think, query transformations. That is an easy session. Directly, you can refer to the Jupyter Notebook. Spend 15 to 20 minutes, most of the things will be pretty much clear.
Krish NAik: Okay, so that project you might need to look into.
Nitesh: Okay, the Notion one, I think, has all the GitHub repositories and all, which I can walk through, right?
Krish NAik: ETIC is from Notion directly, you can look into session-wise. Any problem in between, let me know.
Nitesh: Okay, that would be great. Thanks, thanks, Ankhor, yeah, then I'll follow up.
Krish NAik: Yes.
Krish NAik: Now, Nagesh, your settings are getting 504 gateway timeout issue, timeout issue, alright, fine. Nagesh, I have not tested, really, that endpoint. Okay, I will test it and then let you know.
Krish NAik: Okay, don't worry, Najesh. You don't need to test it today, tomorrow we'll be talking about that, and the CI pipeline with GitHub Actions, that will be tomorrow's agenda. But at least the manual process of deployment, I hope that it will work. In your case, logs are not coming.
Krish NAik: Because the logs… request logs… We can try to do a request, at least.
Krish NAik: Okay, now you've got download here.
Krish NAik: Generally, in your local location, now, command, engine received…
Rajat Khanna: 18… Nope.
Krish NAik: Cccccc, there. AWS ECR, get login password, EUS… see, there is my array.
Krish NAik: Open that file. Can you see here, it's my ID68505. Check that. Oopscooper. Oopscuper.
Krish NAik: Whenever you were doing that login operation, I can see this is mine.
Rajat Khanna: Yellow.
Krish NAik: Wukah.
Rajat Khanna: Because that's the thing I told you, you know, you have to update that file.
Krish NAik: Just wait, let me tell you exactly that file name.
Krish NAik: Because I already told you I remembered to update that file. It was inside, which file? Docker run.aws.json.
Krish NAik: This file I have already told so many times.
Krish NAik: Diane Dietism.
Krish NAik: Do it, do it, Hoja, okay, I know it will work.
Krish NAik: Now, again.
Rajat Khanna: Okay.
Krish NAik: Delete, again, recreate, test it, then let me know tomorrow.
Rajat Khanna: Okay, thank you.
Krish NAik: That was the main con. Culprit was that one.
Krish NAik: Alright, Rajat, so I will stop sharing your one.
Krish NAik: Okay, anybody else?
Krish NAik: Okay? Because if tomorrow's agenda, then simple, next week we'll start with GraphRag. For GraphRag, I was planning to…
Krish NAik: Guys, tell me that, do you guys need Neo 4J? There are much better options in the market, other than Neo 4G.
Krish NAik: Okay, a simple, we will start with Neo 4G, but later on, I will move to Falcon. Okay, so Falcon is very, very good, as compared to, Neo, okay? So, a little bit about that, the things, because the old world uses Neo 4G. How many know about Surreal? Anybody has heard about
Krish NAik: Because, see, the products that I do, because those things come into me, and they are much better than certain cloud services, okay? So, like, I'm just telling you what I am planning right now, as I was working. One is this one.
Krish NAik: I'll go deep.
Krish NAik: Okay, now this is, the actual one. This is very, very good as compared to Neo 4G.
Krish NAik: Okay, very, very fast. You can look into GitHub Trending, the number one repo.
Krish NAik: So, when I, generally, and even to some of my clients, I have suggested it's really good. Now, certain features are not there, for sure, but this is a very, very good project. Okay, and it has its own cloud and other things. So, I'm planning to work with this one. I hope everybody can see my screen.
Krish NAik: Okay? Yes or no? At least write in the chat.
Krish NAik: And the other one that I'm, thinking about, because Neo4J, I think the whole batch knows about Neo4J somewhere you might have heard about this one, okay? But again, see, old stuff is old, because if I show you the same stuff in Falker, I know you can do it. The other one is surreal.
Krish NAik: Now, this is also the multimodal database for AI agents.
Krish NAik: Okay, now, this is also used, like, in a single one, a lot of other supports are there. This I'm planning, let's see, like, at least, because Falker, my content is ready, I've already created the content on Falker. Neo4J Tel Now, I have not created it, but I will create it.
Krish NAik: But, this is really good, like, these two, it got funding also, I think it's a real TV.
Krish NAik: Okay, and majorly all big organizations are actually using it.
Krish NAik: The same things all… there are certain features which are not available in AWS, neither in Azure.
Krish NAik: Okay, there are certain features, such graph-level data, for sure, you can do it, but with respect to certain optimizations.
Krish NAik: Okay? So, why feel that? Let's try to…
Krish NAik: Get our handler team something new or much more trendier.
Krish NAik: Okay, because Neo 4G is… I feel like it's just like the files of vector TVs.
Krish NAik: Alright, so I think…
Krish NAik: That will be next week, we'll be discussing, okay? So, nothing to worry. So, tomorrow, CICD pipeline, a simple pipeline that I'll be building in the GitHub workflows, and then we will start with the deployment. And later on, I have two branches, I will merge this branch with the main one, once my CICD has successfully done it.
Krish NAik: Okay, so tomorrow we'll be continuing about that.
Krish NAik: Alrighty guys, so I think we can conclude the session for today. Let's meet tomorrow and complete this Project 3. So, finally, two projects are remaining.
Krish NAik: Or, multimodal rack project, and finally, your agent's project.
Krish NAik: All right, guys, bye-bye, everyone. Thanks for joining. Let's meet tomorrow and continue our discussion for Project 3.
Krish NAik: By the way, everyone, you guys can talk.